
発話者1  (00:19)
We are engineering here, because I see the talk about how we feel images in the landscape at cuts. Time to get through by 60%. So pretty good basketball, Google star by talking about wisely hatred for hiring. 

発話者1  (00:39)
And why is it that agent model? Then, how we've evolved and adopt change in the life graph. So how we evaluate it and last something listen So why aren't you saying When we talk to swamp business, higher manager And oftentimes, I'm fear that the biggest challenge is hiring pays too much time and hours face that mindful plot out will be just reviewing candidates and deciding to reach out to you and for small sea like startup, that's already 2 days when we thought for any interview that happened. 

発話者1  (01:23)
So that's why and also tiring it and it's not the one shot past that helps the job get perfect kind of things. So you start off some job description, and you see people apply and start to realize how much pure massive environment is actually nice to have or wise enough that you have qualified job descriptions again and Force more people. And then evaluate your activists and again and again, and this is the exact straight of my agent problem. 

発話者1  (02:04)
A soft officer, and that's why we feel cried. And our process we gain with a simple guided and take where our Asian collects your entire requirement and start with the job title. Then, our patient who's generated the job institutions. 

発話者1  (02:25)
And once we conferred and posted the job and our Asians will immediately source obstructive and equivalent beauty, and you can hear invited to apply to your job or provide feedback for our agent. So that our agent will align with your expectation. For day one And once you get replies, I'll hmm, the atmosphere quote based on the qualifications that you find, and you can also set like AI called it, we made into a job. 

発話者1  (02:59)
So at the same time for meaningful conversation with the correct talk and last couple of weeks we can always chat with location. Ask any higher related questions. And it's actually what we have Now we have just seen Al heart rating, alternated an eye process who's talking a little bit more about architecture behind it. 

発話者1  (03:27)
And how we evolved We started with some guiding workflow, where we produce my narrow friendship. All transitions are harmful. We've worked on 2 awesome. 

発話者1  (03:43)
People talk a little bit more dynamic. So we'll be adoptive where we influence the train where sequential execution, while this provides some partial obstruction. But still like the dynamic decisions they need after the and our final breakthrough came with about 2 minute graph. 

発話者1  (04:05)
And this is 16 agents phone optical, where we have a sexual planner that drives a plant-based completely plastic loop and the key of them here is reduced out for the solution. Maybe which takes us some politically more robust, and We just talk about how we shift to aging principle models, in fact, and that's scientists to hardly location. I was flying after many people who were first. 

発話者1  (04:41)
We used a single occasion to specialize in the name and set up the bridges and It's created a process now. We have one board. I have How are this? 

発話者1  (04:54)
After that's responsible for all the high levels and this regime is would take her off. Make sure there's coherent and the loss compacts and localized that population that we have. Our entire workforce operates on a plant is to replace patterns, and this is a dynamic force of landcraft, and finally, you ensure it continues improvement through a full feedback investment on top of those that more like That overall across some of the police circles about the fire is so true and skew, you're able to pursue all the requests about. 

発話者1  (05:42)
So shop, why didn't you take my breath? 

発話者2  (05:50)
As we indicate rock among age 9 super bowls operators are always striking evaluation. So there are reasons first of all, provide hospital levels focused on areas that they can see priority passed in the At night rock to the easy principle that Also, leather specs are AC matching because we have rentals tools. Top a** and that rock use out those purposes. 

発話者2  (06:29)
Not rather than so a lot from the grass means 0 red spots. Destiny. Are basically practices and we move forward. 

発話者2  (06:46)
So we bring into more and more features. And then perhaps that's announced yesterday to our actions, and that's So Being a bread is not only because of a benchmark in style but also because of the whole ecosystem. Ask new robotics connections. 

発話者2  (07:08)
And that's me everywhere. There we go. Next time we're going to talk about how we need to be ground purposes. 

発話者2  (07:22)
To be making and how specifically our current patient does So you tell me there's that As well as our internal systems, including our massive platform. So here are 2 possible memories assistance by cancel communication. I appropriate my former artificial matrix, which stores the tacty street and that's also possible the massacre platform. 

発話者2  (07:54)
Also, there is an underwrite personal mathematic which stores state tackles, and there's also some other amount of applications on top of that, for example, abstract evaporate and mathematics to empower an atmosphere. In terms of the fewer participation. So 18 Asian platforms allow future teams to register their own skills based on Right now, their team are recently and respectfully made use of the higher intensity use for file evaluation. 

発話者2  (08:30)
And applicants use costs to achieve our hospitality Veto wearables, so let's sing as soon as we stop. So if it hasn't already degraded to some extent, for example, the eye in action, how fast the summer is a persistent and hopefully faded test, or even that as well as well and trains for help are supposed to form a manifesto to be sure. So metabolism value very well in narratives, especially in our estimate So the piece is then land rock checkpoints together are actually using our engines. 

発話者2  (09:09)
You can see the size people that alcohol, which also includes this best cross as part of the alcohol, who also have a lot of taxability wrappers, which are going to be for any So especially the top X characters off the ground pressure. For example, there are 2 types of maintenance. First one, you should be passed through. 

発話者2  (09:35)
Oh, our station, I'll grab like hiring intense, not by the African least appetite that's global. Yeah, also a couple of rounds that only reactivated based on case type case. Like any orders much less than 2 years. 

発話者2  (09:54)
For example, this should pass through the national using the phone And this is why I felt a poor are announcing this pair, thanks to the last piece of skill that is provided by athletes Africa that has to introduce population. That's how we actually use a by day R at R beta by a to ask how much so the nose here is at this ID at a roof of cell, which is very powerful switch forward. And coming. 

発話者2  (10:29)
So that's these studies in the foundation. 

発話者1  (10:31)
So we just saw all we leveraged benefits for the opportunity, so that could be a special staff for most people, to understand how we produce this data to make out patients better to talk about evaluation process tests. I was starting with a lot of ways with sentiment captured, at least Pace that will everything that's with that capacity. Not just the final as of a food chase the context, possibly two people 2 offs and also like every position sat down. 

発話者1  (11:12)
However, lately policy is not able to send everything to a stand for our production data. So we will completely similar comparing what outlets can test, and together we sat those data into our human annotation. And also, albums. 

発話者1  (11:34)
I've been reaching a vocabulary and once a staff of all kinds like this. And that final staff is the optimized and today, what is we will mentally define, and we sold our prompts involved to based on what the Constitution surface and the path forward is entered, which is what we just learned yesterday as well, and we're looking forward to integrated and close our continuous learning without too much human. Today? 

発話者1  (12:13)
So we just talk about how age evolved and how we architect and decided and along with journey of students adopted agents, we have some lessons in color for the shares thing. The lesson one that brought to a bipartisan process constraints determines the real architecture. So as strong as opposed a lot of box, Halloween integrated lens in primitive how they were useful and powerful that, however, not everyone fit into obvious things. 

発話者1  (12:49)
And the story behind this lesson is we have our agent washing up, who it works as one of these suggestions. For example, it will say looks like we're moving. Candidates with free without a degree in Computer Science topic. 

発話者1  (13:07)
So it's application requirements, really a mask. Stop. We want you to do this. 

発話者1  (13:14)
So, what's next is the new circuit? Either say, yes or no, that Interesting part is they can just walk away or completely change their topics talking apps. I am so our first establishment was using bedrock to draw it in this During the cost, you should never know backward. 

発話者1  (13:35)
The graph and wait for the influence of the concern and reason to exacerbate spots. And this And clean, yes, however, Elizabeth is a Little bit on YouTube space. So we build contact with humanity. 

発話者1  (13:55)
So every important graph and to end and at the end of the graph we will persist, minimal cost turned contacts in the example that I mentioned we'll see stories something like suggest you think application requirement as waiting for users to suffer and for the next message. Top in outside groups is that balance between this address, who we want to compromise rejected over that to something else, meaning we wait for the contacts we explore. Was this opera particular status scale? 

発話者1  (14:34)
Lsd, who we pressed a state and also keeping our conversation back to the most important. Is we control object on the size? Not tracking, we are just persistent with minimal contact and shots. 

発話者1  (14:52)
Let us talk about why as the importance of all ages. And why take this path? 

発話者2  (15:03)
Yeah, a lot of stars are always taken out. But any species should be more determined in space, especially bars is not partisan aristocracy, and as we all know, with the improvements of a model capability, a lot of the area could eventually replace. We're awesome, delayed fast. 

発話者2  (15:23)
We are always somewhere on the highest genome across the network, and that's the optimization and That's the depreciation, and that's how we make a succeed in China. So especially if you want to share a few lessons that we learned about how to do the high scenery. So they are getting better at filters who are user requirements. 

発話者2  (15:50)
So you don't see a castle of courtes. So the priority for price engineering are really different. For example, going to focus on the practice and then these categories corporations about both these kinds of final answer to these. 

発話者2  (16:03)
Despite different approaches based on the shopping data, the needs for glass broadly state purchasing action boundaries to secure the safety. And we deliver the entire events want to ensure As long as our transplant compliance So there are carbon batteries. Here's the tallest matchment aspect of being talking about all the time. 

発話者2  (16:30)
So check what's going to be summarization. As well as contrast companies, naturalized providers have companies which Canada have. So this tells David what needs to remember. 

発話者2  (16:45)
And all the format episodes was sometimes love that aims to be consistently a prosecutor plan. So we have to confirm confirmation. And follow back to optimal gatherings out with correlation programmatic responses that will be illustrates. 

発話者2  (17:04)
So how the agents know what they universities? Thus, no changes organisms. For example, when Oscar white knows execution, I always want to make sure the next film, instead of making certain rather than a rather than talking all staff, we need the draw where she had a few brokers. 

発話者2  (17:28)
They were like a big black screen. White saw food artists or whites and 2 voltage, hot blacks or a server about Alzheimer's times and secondly, tools That will be called either. Another clue, rather than so these issues. 

発話者2  (17:49)
What data adjusts? So this is all the price, dairy artists get better and better closer and closer to our customer firms. And that's something We're already faculty, so our all here's probably our names and cardiated, gross 
