
発話者1  (00:14)
Thank you so much for being here. I am at me. I believe Vice President of product at a bridge and excited to chat about training AI and engaged in really high speeds and highly regulated industries. 

発話者1  (00:28)
And you know, a little bit about some of our journeys. So just hand a little bit of context about rich. We are a clinical intelligence platform. 

発話者1  (00:38)
We started solving involvement, tools for clinicians, solving as many of their clerical and clinical forces as possible, growing starting as the education clinician oxygen. There are over 2 billion conversations that happened every single year. There may be less and we think that the conversation is probably one of the most important workloads in welfare is obviously aware of patients. 

発話者1  (01:04)
And clinicians and doctors are getting and was eating care. But if you think about the 20% of our GDP that those horse healthcare, so much of it is downstream or a derivative of that conversation, whether it's the notes, the billing codes, the trains, the prior observations, the medications and wherever at date, the first products that we built is we built the infrared product and with customer value to capture this conversation, which is historically been fully on the structure data and determine into a clinically useful chart or not for doctors and animals today where there's a massive doctor in the country, especially those in and doctors are running out, they spend 10 to 20:00 after hours. 

発話者1  (01:56)
We've done a really good job behind celebrating our lives and these crimes. And now that we have all of this data have gotten into this wedge for the most frankflow, then do products that we can build it, our ability to help us deliver our seconds, which are, how do we help us learn the state and make more money? And given clinicians, for opening our app before during an after a patient lost in the room might be actually stabilized and we stay back in the volume. 

発話者1  (02:25)
So with that, we've scaled the way we're at 250 of the largest law systems in the country available supplies larger than the world. And we've also put ourselves in the center of healthcare's data layer. The most important signal on healthcare has historically, like I said, been on a structure. 

発話者1  (02:46)
After and because we now have this scale and it has all of this data we manage to get all of these unparalleled data network. We have over a 100 million conversations that happen on our platform. Because with the arabs that we received as well as suddenly from our customers, we're able to de identify it and we're learning constantly, whether it's edits, people are making short notes, queries, people are asking what are encouraging AI agent and using that term supermodels and continuously evaluate with our apple live and keep an evaluations and continue to deploy better and better products so that it can pass over time. 

発話者1  (03:27)
And I've all heard about the company and decided to actually get into a content, which is, what does it mean to actually build AI? And agents in these high seats, high trust environments. There are a few things that shape all of our products, business and technical decisions. 

発話者1  (03:43)
I think the first one is the bar for what we can shift is just incredibly high. And so velocity can't come at the expense of quality. The reason for that is the states are quite high. 

発話者1  (03:55)
If we incorrectly label evacuation or a message that has real patient safety implications and hipaa, and the light that we abuse and take care of phy data not to shape every decision that we make. And finally, especially in enterprise healthcare buyers are choosing who they'll even talk to, based on security interest, something that we like to say internally is trust and turning drops, that lost their buckets and certainly now that any single model release that has a massively negative implications to have that customers Philosopher 2 quake case studies to show how we acknowledge chef quickly, despite all of these things that we're thinking about constantly. 

発話者1  (04:40)
While we're at first, put our core, nose stops and then move on to our agent system which is what we've got. So the notice is great for doctors are the corrupt is how they landed at the scale that he did. Basic biologists is a doctor who will open her up. 

発話者1  (04:59)
They'll report the conversation that has the patient insect and will turn that into a clinical use. We'll chart our notes that then get smitted into the electronic record. Now, if there really are, it's not just a sovereignty of a meeting or a conversation and the reason for that is the note that we create ultimately becomes fulfilled the thing that hospital and the doctor gets complicated for so accuracy is extremely important. 

発話者1  (05:25)
And all of this also becomes part of the patient's longitudinal record and quality matters in ways that I think a lot of economic products don't experience a few examples. If we have misattributation in our ribs, so a note set might assign a statement or symptom or a decision to the wrong person we have really, really large medical and legally significant ramifications. For example, a patient saying that they have a symptom is very different than a doctor explicitly diagnosing it. 

発話者1  (05:58)
And for it, and if you're diagnosing it knowing the wrong thing, there will be a severe consequences for upcoming or downcom. So I'm allowed to be congratulations or hallucinations if we are putting orders for our medication that wasn't actually prescribed or putting the wrong message. Huge, huge huge patient baby issues. 

発話者1  (06:19)
As we pass some of these issues at an internal testing with the biggest aim in trying to experiment with our release process, namely getting the confidence being needed to actually show Prior to some of the changes being made a while ago, polices would take us anywhere from 1 to 2 months and we had clinicians, annoating data running labels, labelers and a lot of custom tools that I'm going to talk to each other. And we have measure approached across the platforms we chose the actual ways in which we hope one. 

発話者1  (06:54)
And then finally, just fiddle human operational process improvements from a platform perspective. We migrantulate rap we were using too many of our own asset custom tools, and as we were scaling, they weren't growing all over these pieces and lanecraft gave us humanified Datasets, annotation tracing evaluation in one system and from an enterprise security perspective. We were allowed to solve those. 

発話者1  (07:22)
And also have the access controls and audit facility needed. And we use linkedins for our email software. It gave us all the customization. 

発話者1  (07:32)
We needed from a UI perspective, and I gave it across altitudes whether it was debugging, a simple empower, or seeing across all long places performance. You could do it in one place. From an actual improvement perspective, we generally have the gifts of a lot of people. 

発話者1  (07:53)
And how important this product is to clinician workflows and across all of the clinician and New Jersey facts, new products. And outer products. We have a whole issue a whole list of model issues and we want to improve When you were prioritized, hit 5 months. 

発話者1  (08:10)
So how often was it happening as well as the summary of an issue? If we got it wrong for the states really And with that, the organized all of these novel issues into an aggregate set of pillars, simply things like accuracy, compliance, style, latest, and we started to go one by one. And create judges against these policies It is originally it was pretty comfortable. 

発話者1  (08:36)
We would have a clinician who made the subject matter. Well, designed by an annotation guide to labeled encounters, and then someone would actually iterate on prompts. To get the judge to match the commercial levels really slow. 

発話者1  (08:50)
We moved to an APO framework, and it now takes annotation guides and the label patterns and generates the tolerant judge buys The thing that always keeps me up and I are just making sure that the underlying data is actually correct in high quality. Because this is the basis of evergrande, we do a few things that are very helpful to us, we make sure that the annotations are actually matching the accepted outputs of our llf genes. We also like to collect free text exclamations from our annotators. 

発話者1  (09:26)
Obviously when there are issues or an inconsistencies that allow us to speak. But more importantly, when things aren't broken, we ask for it, because it allows us to check that the people who are annoating and evaluating are actually paying attention. And so people are just looking through. 

発話者1  (09:42)
This is a good way to really understand the quality of our data. And then finally always think about what is actually expertise made up front. There's certain evaluation or Datasets for being made of board service acquisition. 

発話者1  (09:57)
Sometimes you might need a specialist but learning about that's very, very impressive. Another design decision that's worth calling out is how we use both rappers, free and profit space stretches to make sure that we have a lending approach to several players that complement each other. We have reference free judges, they generalize across all encavers, and they'll look at the notes and the conversation and explore it. 

発話者1  (10:25)
And it doesn't need an old standard note to compare next. Then, that means we can run them offline before importantly online, at all times continuously monitor the quality of They definitely have limits if there's a lot of encounter specific view on the specificity that gets met. And no sort of so inherently suspected. 

発話者1  (10:47)
So we supplement it with reference to these stretches that get exposed as the specialty level. And what these 2 approaches were able to have really high confidence in what we're serving. And even though what these emails I say that we can't push the product just because of the states that we're operating in offline emails happen, first, they now have been very, very quickly with the process. 

発話者1  (11:14)
They're really easy, but you still back us to get this historical encounters also very quick and admit something about Nike Morty to the industry that we're operating in is the way in which we view may be testing. When I first started bridge, I never thought, maybe testing would be possible in healthcare at the sacrifice level. So because I worked at dress, we've gotten explicit vibes from a set of our Partners and customers who said, give it what you're doing upstream. 

発話者1  (11:41)
I'm okay with a silent police without knowing about it. And remind your first time to 15% of customers willing to make with you that's a way of privileging a lot of trust that means heat, but it allows us to let the gap for more signal are people editing the note. What are the ratings? 

発話者1  (11:59)
We're leaving are beginning, really, really loudest back, and this is usually signalable and snowy isn't so in that final gives us the confidence to actually go through a full release, and we'll do our containers offline monitoring. The hardest would take us 1 to 2 months, and now we can get through this. In phase and get a place where we're visiting all updates. 

発話者1  (12:22)
We don't really know about this. And so really exciting, we've seen improvements over the past few quarters in making sure that we can continue to develop fine. And more currently, our users, our bias, what we should also let they feel it instantly. 

発話者1  (12:43)
Now I'll move on to the second case. Study notes are the foundation of what we do. And we felt on top, a more generic, a branch assistant, and generally we want to help clinicians make the best decisions they can at the right moment with the right context. 

発話者1  (13:01)
But the reality is most tools that permissions use today, Yale adoption and heart will use. There's a lot of constraints. Personal doctors are very busy. 

発話者1  (13:12)
They're going back-to-back 15 minute appointments, they don't have the time to pull something up, look up the contacts of a patient, a lot of existing tools also make them choose between security or no security and with these fragmented workflows, what we did was build a unified agent that persists. Across the workloads, so before The Visit during that visit. After The Visit, there is a uniform us and agents and we decided to hold a lot of our features and capabilities into one vehicle. 

発話者1  (13:48)
That was really composable capabilities. The examples are capabilities like being able to search patient contacts across multiple systems on record or actually doing actions like editing their notes or placing a medication or an MRI. And then, finally enabling something like clinical decision support. 

発話者1  (14:09)
So the doctor has a question. Can we support them via really searching against literature that comes from elevated medical weapons? And instead of these multiple features, looking in different places, having it as a singular patient allows us to collect school at the right time, but also deliver William coherent experience. 

発話者1  (14:32)
From work on product perspective, these are some of the principles that we use in building this to make sure that we weren't overwhelming our doctors and clinicians. The first is we like to say that we try to feel like air conditioning. We want to be on in the background, making things better but not have to actively be present unless we think there's something really important. 

発話者1  (14:55)
The second is the agency in healthcare. Especially is really, really important that clinicians know that their control we might be able to suggest things. But ultimately, we want permissions to use all the data and the make the right decisions. 

発話者1  (15:11)
The third is responsive this symptom is that a lot of different forms. If a clinician is explicitly given us against a feedback, we want to make sure that our Fires and systems are actively listening and improving my plane. But because of where we operate, we also can implicitly learn a lot to make the production higher. 

発話者1  (15:34)
So this might be, if a clinician is constantly making the same edit so I don't know. Can we weather their style to automatically apply the small future? Or give it the context that we have that, the patients the, clinician is seeing have might be suggested through this agent things, that they might ask at certain moments of The Visit with the patient to deliver that care And as we built this, I think some more underlying machine learning from an email perspective. 

発話者1  (16:04)
But the complexity of a attitude just because we're not now using simple setballs, some of the evap criteria that I thought about clinical quality is that actually accurate safety? Are we making sure that this agent isn't actively? Patient down 3 and adversary testing what is happening at the edges, making sure that the agent isn't answering questions on things like, isn't answering questions that I wasn't trying to do. 

発話者1  (16:35)
And finally, for the tools selection first effective is the agent, making the right school and behaving the way that financial response So what happen? I think the 2 takeaways. I hope set up Facebook and first. 

発話者1  (16:50)
You don't have to sacrifice on velocity and make the war quality, and if you invest in the right ego. And the structure of And are real and really specific on the things on which your product needs to get right? You believe both quickly and you probably know the outputs of your product. 

発話者1  (17:07)
Even largely and second, maybe more of a personal medical playlist has decided some hopes to potentially think about building in healthcare. I think from an impact perspective. Healthcare is probably where we need some of our best filters, and there's probably no more universal or more problem, given 20% of our GDP is going towards 0. 

発話者1  (17:30)
They just from the largest businesses look at created and given the high-stakes. The next 1B hard to say. Confidence will also be solved here. 

発話者1  (17:39)
So thank you so much for reminding me to join the rest of your day and 
