
発話者1  (00:01)
And that's because we really think that agencies are at the center of mediation, development, life cycles. Each agent phrase factors, the unique behavioral record of what your agent actually did at a specific point in time. That being said Agent crazy. 

発話者2  (00:22)
I'm working. 

発話者1  (00:23)
Occasional observability poses a unique data infrastructure problem. For one agent traces are very deeply connected and can contain thousands if not tens of thousands of intermediate sets. He payloads associated with agent traces are large and undoubted. 

発話者1  (00:46)
These 2 characteristics of agent traces are a direct result of agents running through a longer time. Horizon and LLM context, window sizes getting larger and larger. We're seeing an increased number of Asian traces being logged with modalities such as images and voice. 

発話者1  (01:09)
Voice is getting especially popular with applications like customer support. Finally, the access patterns for the current patterns needed to effectively mine. Your agent's faces for useful insights are unique and complex. 

発話者1  (01:29)
Ancient traces are not only encoding more information and getting more complicated. They're also growing in volume as agents become more and more ubiquitous. Here's the figure that highlights the real dance customers. 

発話者1  (01:44)
Weekly trace volume over time. As you can see, in the early stages of testing an involvement, the weakly trans volumes are relatively small. But as the agent and his production and as new agents entered the breaker, the weekly face volume that we now see is over a 150 million. 

発話者1  (02:09)
So as mentioned earlier The Palos associated with agent racism are large and they're getting bigger Uber time. Over the past couple of years Have you seen the P50 table size associated with agent traces, central banks? Grow from 6 KB to 30 centimet, KB and 399 has grown from still pretty sizable. 

発話者1  (02:34)
364 KB to 12 MB, that And another vehicle plan Earlier this year we had a single customer spent a 50 TB of trace data on a single day. That's quite a lot of data. This video highlights what a modern Asian trace enlightenment. 

発話者1  (02:57)
Looks like in practice, as you can see, lots of intermediate steps very deeply nested this trace was actually pulled from one of our internal photo market agents that's built with deep agents and another thing to point out is that this trace actually encodes 8.1 million tokens. Traditional data infrastructure was not built for the challenges. Associated with aging observability If you're using stuff, optimal infrastructure to handle hooks and ability to workload, you will experience low ferries in a congestion moment. 

発話者1  (03:37)
You're also experiencing rising infrastructure costs and complexity as you try to scale up. When you're iterating on your agent, you cannot afford to have slow and cumbersome interactions with your agent trace. And so today, we're super excited to be watching this TV. 

発話者1  (04:03)
This TV is the database repurposed built for agents that are ability to work with. We've been working on Smith TV for the past few months and are incredibly excited by the results that we're seeing in production. Please stay cute for this video to learn a little bit more. 

発話者2  (04:19)
Introducing Smith eating the database purpose bill for agent observability. This is a trace, a referendum area that does how it thinks decides and performs now a mention. 

発話者3  (04:32)
Million. 

発話者2  (04:32)
Earlier this day, because agents are everywhere. The problem is that traces aren't like traditional logs and metrics that are larger. Equally, nested multimodal Ao querier than the same way. 

発話者2  (04:45)
You're switching across the text and meaning in traditional databases. They weren't built for this so as Tracy's. Growth is slow until now. 

発話者2  (04:56)
Smith dv, the database purpose built for agent observability. Search across poultry content query the entire agent conversations access complex data instantly and at scale. The only thing you have to reliable agents requires rapid integration. 

発話者2  (05:12)
With Smith TV, you can move from data to insight to improvement faster 

発話者1  (05:27)
That video got me pretty high done. Whoever is creating a video between an amazing job. So now let's take a post a look at what's going to be actually is and how it's architected. 

発話者1  (05:40)
The first thing to point out is that 50D is backed by optic story. This gives us a united property. First optic storage is incredibly cheap, and it scales pretty much infinite. 

発話者1  (05:53)
The second is it gives us what's called compute story separation. This allows us to elastically scale the services that vaccine need without any complex shuffling or charting the data and just give us Third, this gives us an architecture that is relatively easy to set up in solving those requirements where data is resident requirements are strict. Now, at high level, the length and services, necklace and TV. 

発話者1  (06:27)
After getting assignments from our cluster managers, our cluster manager helps ensure that vote is evenly distributed across our servers and also maintains some semblance of what's called sticky route sticky routine is important. Because it helps utilize cash. And it also helps batch for data effectively for industrial So during adjusting trace data comes through adjusting service, it gets scratched, and it gets thoroughly stored to office storage. 

発話者1  (06:58)
These files are registered in a postgrad menus store. I work at times we figure out which files are necessary to be scanned. So the queries we download them from object storage, and we scan them. 

発話者1  (07:11)
We also heavily utilize SSD, cashing and memory to minimize ground tricks to object score. Finally, we have some action service that helps shape her files for more optimism. Smith TV is specifically designed for agent observability, access patterns The whole walk through some of these access patterns in the next few slides. 

発話者1  (07:39)
50 feet makes Putin into individual phrases and individual intermediate steps really snapping back 18 observability isn't just about asking what happened across millions of phrases. It's also about asking, you know what happened in this one particular Asian executive That's why random access is really important and something that we've optimized since beauty. Ancient traces have been contained megabytes of tax data. 

発話者1  (08:15)
And oftentimes you need to search across your agent faces using keywords for phrases. As you can see, the TV makes voltage search really snappy and interact to accomplish this where you actually built a custom inverted ax layout specifically designed for opticosteria. Ancient interactions are often multi turned in nature. 

発話者1  (08:46)
This is why friends are first class derivative within lengths. Now that threads are backwards, because you need to see how snappy interactive, it is to drill down into multicurnation interact. In the age of November golden workload. 

発話者1  (09:07)
You often need to pick specific time. Horizon and apply filters like on metadata, tags, nave, lacing, key and other actions. Scanning is filtering speed is something that we highly optimize in TV. 

発話者1  (09:23)
And as you can see, the results are nearly as different. We're incredibly pleased by the performance that, since TV brings the length across these key patients worldwide. Compared to divorce and np, these lengthened foreclosed are now anywhere from 6X to 15X to faster than before. 

発話者1  (09:49)
This is absolutely magical. Oh, look, there's this thing. I'll return, we're super lucky to be working with customers like play and manta who were early adopters of Smith and As you can see, Jeff replay and Annie fermanta wrote state. 

発話者1  (10:13)
How Smith TV has completely transformed their experience interacted with their traces within life. So 50 feet is purpose built for patients, infertibility, and we've built it using a modern X stat. The entire system is written in drugs, and these 2 often open source projects. 

発話者1  (10:35)
One is called Apache data fusion, which is an expensible rust based frame. The second is vortex, which is an extensible file format that allows us to take custom encodings and company strategies for the different columns. That was solid On top of this foundation, we have heavily, we've added some Peggy customization. 

発話者1  (11:00)
Around indexing, specifically for voltaix search, we've added custom prayer planning and execution plans, and we also have invested in custom storage layouts for all the data that we're storing within synopsy. Here are some of the technical challenges that we've had to solve when buildings and TVS, so just a few of them like a lot, but I'm going to choose 

発話者3  (11:27)
So 

発話者1  (11:28)
Engage sensor building workflows. Your fans are distributed. They come in different parts, and this is because agents run along right and so you can have a start event that starts or gets a better sense. 

発話者1  (11:43)
Sometimes hours before you're into that And so, finding and merging these distributed events together at free time in our compassion, time is a technical challenge that we had to solve doing it efficiently is something that we could invest for a lot of times A lot of the queries within the mice, men are top case outwards. So they contain an orderbite limit and a more naive word plan would essentially climb all the files that are in range and hand them out and do some type of merge and copy operation. 

発話者1  (12:19)
This is actually like a little bit expensive. An object storage? And she's quite expensive on optic storage. 

発話者1  (12:26)
So what we've done is we've taken a time window based approach and encoded back into custom execution plan that the hop pay salberry within Finally, in observability, workloads, you often need to serve the most recently ingested data as fast as possible, right? And in order to do that, what we do is we've buffered data in the ingestion service. Even after it's been durablely flushed through option scores. 

発話者1  (12:59)
And we buffer it in memory and on SSD. And we made that data available to inquiry service to avoid downloading a ton of small files for leading extraordin. Langston performing is not only important but human us, but also agent us Increasingly agents are not just a thing that are being observed by landscapes. 

発話者1  (13:29)
They're also the users of language And it's a huge fit to have your agents slow down by inefficient fuel. I really like this book from Jeff Dean, who states that, you know, as we get Asian base systems that are operating multiple times faster than a human Your tools and anal spawn. We're super excited to announce that smithy bee is now serving 4 observability workloads across all of us cloud homelands. 

発話者1  (14:04)
If you're using landsmith on Smith, Langston dot top all of your interactions in your tracing project page are now powered by Smith TV. Soon We're working quickly to get the rest of the language that you buy back some TVS and we're going to bring in students who cell posted and across all of vocal cloud traffic. So specifically sets a really, really strong technical foundation for everything that we want to build into land and just share some more exciting updates about landscape. 

発話者1  (14:41)
I'd like to welcome Harrison. The island state. Thank you so much. 

発話者2  (14:57)
Smith smith TV is absolutely incredible. As you can see. I have the fun and easy job where it's talking about what we built but on fish and the whole team there goes out and builds really complex engineering projects and databases that help power everything. 

発話者2  (15:11)
Involved in bicycle, and that's really how we think about what we do want to accelerate everything in this life cycle. We think traces and Smith D are a key part of that, and so with this solid foundation, a big part of what we're thinking about now is how can we accelerate this life cycle even more? Because even with Chris's even with absorbability, the visibility that it provides is table stakes being able to see what your agent did at each step is absolutely needed. 

発話者2  (15:39)
But that's a table stakes. It's still hard to spin this iteration wide will finding issues among the tens of thousands hundreds of thousands millions of traces that you have is still hard. When you find those traces, understanding issues in them is still hard. 

発話者2  (16:00)
That can be really, really long. You have to comb through them and see exactly where the L is testing app, where it's all in the wrong pool. Once you understand that issue fixing, that is hard, you want to change the throng you want to change the code, you want to change some tools. 

発話者2  (16:15)
There's a bunch of different things that you have to investigate and try to dive back after the core issue. I'm going to want you to fix it before you were keeping these issues as hard. Sometimes it can feel like lack of when you fix one thing and then you know, you change the prompt and it reappears. 

発話者2  (16:30)
So how do you avoid this? And so we spend a lot of time thinking about how we can spin-off this flywheel faster and faster, because it is so far all these things I mentioned are so annoying. And so, what do you do? 

発話者2  (16:45)
When you have a lot of really annoying things that are hard and important that you don't want to do you build an engine to help you with it, of course. And so that's why today we're really excited to launch an agent in landscape. An ambien proactive action picking agent that we're calling lansmith engine. 

発話者2  (17:12)
Specifically, what it does is it will sit on top of your traces. It'll go through them on a schedule in the background. It will detect issues and assign a priority to them. 

発話者2  (17:23)
It will back into evidence with traces and then it will suggest concrete resolution actions. We've been working with a number of Starbucks over the past few weeks to roll this out for them. And as you can see, it is already proactively suggesting beatholes to add and code issues to make, and that has dramatically reduced time to detection and time to trial. 

発話者2  (17:46)
So specifically, what enzymes can do? It? Acts at all stages of this life cycle. 

発話者2  (17:51)
So it sits on top of traces. It can suggest code changes. If you hook it up to your gig Hubbard code base, it can suggest data points to add to Datasets. 

発話者2  (17:59)
So that you can use these data to avoid regressions in the future. If you connect it to prompter context up, it can suggest changes there. And then it can also suggest online emails to add so that you can track these issues over time. 

発話者2  (18:13)
Let's see a little video of it in actuality. 

発話者2  (19:33)
Blame Smith pension is in public data as of today, so I already see some people on laptops log on to lane, Swiss and try it out. Overall, as a company, we're building the entire platform for the Asian development. Life cycle. 

発話者2  (19:50)
Over the past few years, we've been building a lot of the different apps and infrastructure pieces from electricity and evaluations and prop pub. That help power a lot of this life cycle. Today we launched Smith TV as a foundational database to power all of this. 

発話者2  (20:08)
And we built landsmith engine as an agent that sits on top and helps you spin this flywheel, faster and faster. More than just a platform. We also want to be a partner to everyone in this room in this community. 

発話者2  (20:23)
And the entire space in general Hi, guys. Why we're really thrilled about me from general. This is the opportunity to interrupt your day and then take a pause and learn from us. 

発話者2  (20:36)
But also other presenters and other Partners in the ecosystem and other companies and other people that are sitting next to and I would encourage everyone to take full advantage of not only today but also tomorrow as soon as And so, in order to really get the day started, I want to introduce your guide for the next 2 days, Jake from Lankton. 

発話者4  (21:12)
Good morning, everyone and welcome to day one of interrupt. 2026. I didn't interrupt last year. 

発話者4  (21:23)
The big question was naked, actually work in production this year. It seems the answer is yes may have dashboards. Escalation paths and mandatory compliance due by We're excited to kick things off, and you can't wait for an incredible day. 

発話者4  (21:39)
Ahead before we get started. Our view Chris' house Steven reminders to help make the experience seamless for everyone. First, today's full agenda is available via Qatar on the screen. 

発話者4  (21:51)
Be sure to scan it and follow along compared to your session. Thank you to all of our amazing speakers, we have an incredible layout ahead, and we're thrilled to have you here with us today. So let's speakers will be available for Q and age following that session. 

発話者4  (22:09)
Happy, ask me anything desks in land channel and hq. We also want to extend a huge thank you to our presenting sponsor Cisco, customer experience. I'm personally had the chance to work first thing together with this team and they're doing big things around building customer experience things. 

発話者4  (22:31)
If you show the visiting on Michigan street and stay tuned palace presentation later this morning. Also, thanks to all our sponsors, make sure to check out their demos at the booth over the next few days. A quick reminder about patches, and for those of you who didn't get them. 

発話者4  (22:51)
Please remember going to grab them at the registration desk at break. You can type these badges together with one another to instantly exchange contact information and all of your connections will be shared with you after the event. Your bathroom also light up when there are 5 minutes remaining in the break. 

発話者4  (23:08)
And before your pre-registered workshop section. Your cues start making your way back to the stage for your workshop. But wipe my access and the network is land chain interrupt, and the password is observed. 

発話者4  (23:27)
And finally, for everybody's safety coming comfort, please keep backpacks and personal items, touch under the desk undersea prime. So the aisles will be put That's also right. Let's get there when I started. 

発話者4  (23:39)
Please join me in welcoming Carlos. Perreo from Cisco customer experience to this day. 

発話者3  (23:58)
Good morning, everyone. Thanks for having me here. Is I was on the backstage watching accusations for the last time? 

発話者3  (24:10)
So financials in the United States from San Francisco and recurrent speakers and the idea for today is going through the next 10 minutes or so, this is very high level agenda. So what is the ancestor this qualified? So that's one slice of set the context and we talk about the renewals, the genetic system. 

発話者3  (24:31)
But the people that want to see it last year, ancestral next thing, how we view the gender before reduce this, what a complex district is at 56 north of 60 peaks in and north business one and a 1 of business returns revenue. So this team is in charge of all the equipment revenue of By the way, the announcement earnings today. So hopefully we'll do well, that's that's a very interesting thing. 

発話者3  (24:57)
And then we are gonna carry you better. Learn not only on how we evolve the renewed suspects because, many of you last year came out to be like this problem I. Have essentially myself in my mind, infrastructure in Italy. 

発話者3  (25:13)
That's what I'm experiencing science issues as an organization involved 18th attending through 10000 people depend. How good is this? And we have a very stunted process of land about expanding the Union that makes there is a bunch of teams underneath there on the Capitol stats. 

発話者3  (25:29)
Land is pretty much inquired that by central system. It's a sustainable since you start to use right away, but if it's a piece of hardware or many of those, there is someone that needs to go down Iraq and stack the pupil in all of this. So we have the deliberate team. 

発話者3  (25:44)
The professional service across the countries to make this voice, and there are multiple customers of ours that are multiple georechers. They have here, Asia and us can not forget that you have a business success organization where they're only planning that they have the multiple people organization that their mission life is to maximize the value of the investment at some DNA system. So if someone by the higher license and using a basic functionality know that everything should use AL we're going to be satisfied and if that is the case, we usually enjoy expansions or the use case and stuff that's to a point that reduced cycle, then end up with everything is good given, a mess up customers not being solved immediately, that's possible. 

発話者3  (26:29)
So when you look for their lens That's going to be when Henderson's public company was the GPT has a wall effect, and everything was abused by ChatGPT but that was a business to consumer capitalism. Our customer experience is only to be so we start with the chef. What's kind of things where if you go to the sector that represents the last year you saw that we focus on how many funding private advised, use cases are supposed to go after that higher effect. 

発話者3  (26:58)
So the best year the whole team was about to dense data. Everybody spoke about the dense AI. How it gets into the compost test starts. 

発話者3  (27:06)
Patients let me talk about orchestration. We believe that in many famous states, you stay here where a lot of corporations like themselves. A lot of companies is going to start to look at the business workflows, that logic is the phone a lot of the business transferflows out there and many of those have been created easier, which means that a lot of people using AI to augment that's a nice world AI in some of those workflows to plow planned victory since nature efficiency is more prosperous. 

発話者3  (27:39)
It is more independent is more whatever effective but here, many times actually on our case. If I have a word for that stroke and I'm doing AI actually got to the broken faster so we realized that we're pissing off customers sometimes faster than we used to deal with A. So I'm gonna tell you this isn't reality, but trying to look at how the degree composed. 

発話者3  (28:01)
AI need to work close and use our ideas and methods to judge success as opposed to just saying performance methods from that. With that in mind, we now realize that the majority of the value that can be measured is when you go after a united native business world elaborate technologies like the one that are going to announce, if I hear someone who pushed to make this hackfield, but the reality returns of the content is still transitioning for the shot was to the intense AI to something. So how did that happen? 

発話者3  (28:33)
First, in trying to find, we had run into production. The transformation we didn't have 50 BI have so many ideas that the team that you're going to go out for them. But outside of this, we have the identification, which was a Mutti agent based on Chatbot interface. 

発話者3  (28:49)
Initially, we have a guided interface, so we use GenAI just for the answer. You're gonna have to for the questions. Because the renewal seed paper is what they want answers for not less like 3 months until they don't let us, I don't want to be slave for me, because in the open front, but the name for days at the beginning was actually earned the source of the team to use the system. 

発話者3  (29:12)
But soon enough, you realized that this alarm wasn't enough, and we involved the systems. What is run into the reproduction? Which is the notion of a teammate? 

発話者3  (29:22)
So the idea that teammate is actually focused on the workflows, not only on the patients, because the workflows run the business as the agent needs to be a mistake when they should get here, and the idea is to how we get a steam name to delegates to receive some tests and be able to prove that out of this. So that's why I'm going to both easily detain more people. So we have it running in production that stays today. 

発話者3  (29:45)
We opened up needing anybody who can type anything. It's not kind of grand student interface and you can't be available to all these, so let's dive a little bit differently. So I show to everybody how we do the death collection. 

発話者3  (30:01)
So we have renewed agents, and we have a sentiment analysis agent, because the Christmas piece of likely good for renewable increases, then you have an abduction. Agent, so the higher the adoption, the higher the likelihood of the produce so that Jesus has been brought, we have discovered agents. You run an open practice environment using multiple models. 

発話者3  (30:22)
And we also had a machine learning risk prediction model. You know very well that elements and predictions don't get a lot very well. So you build the ML model traditional one a high level predictions. 

発話者3  (30:33)
So that combination papers, 95% of accuracy, and a lot of set occasions is on the way it didn't work like that. So we need to improve to the notion of the religious demand and that's where a lot of interesting things happen. When we realize is that the supervisor you start to actually get more complex as you start to get more combinatorial, more questions and more analysis, the reason that it needs to happen, so you need to introduce the notion of a planet, something that the orchestration, based on the context of the question will need, I want a spot to break how to plan the decomposition of agents and surpasses. 

発話者3  (31:16)
It's an interesting thing, because the better the models get today. The more recently they have, the more creative they get as well. So then they can get out of what the business is depart. 

発話者3  (31:28)
So for an architecture perspective, we have no producer based, not only the short parts for the UI. You have produces an Adi, because other systems can consume that and you go for a supervisor graft and the supervisor graft, actually the planet being offensive stages, and every stage can have steps. So from the feedback step, you go and everything is okay you move on. 

発話者3  (31:51)
If not, you need to replay. And come back to say, hey, this is a supervisor you're an analysis of a planet the planet didn't go as planned. So let's be planted. 

発話者3  (32:00)
So and then from that we go to Asian players on this example, we have renewed production sentiment presentation, and then now if you select a Renaissance, the renewable station itself is a subtract. So we have a planet inside itself, because you can't have 2 agents and you see how this becomes recurrent, and you can see how what convolution and error was talk about. Let me become more and more interesting. 

発話者3  (32:27)
So if I go to this, what change instead of having a supervisor eating the agent, we have an option on a plan. It implies some changes on our production at stake again. I'm talking about here here. 

発話者3  (32:42)
Brandy seeks finish up and beat them. So you cannot mess around with this kind of thing. And you talk about the scale. 

発話者3  (32:48)
So the supervisor it is a high level plan that masks task for agents or soon grasps that adventure, that agents, it is not an honorable, it's not something that is going to codify all the forms a lot of the training for people's life data, have a supervisor the supervisor because he smart so I have a best model out there. I'm waiting for it and then a supervisor in terms of light 1000 lights on food that we realize hey, it's not so make the supervised as witnessed as possible. He just needs to think validated policy how to rouse, and you can let the land graph routing for that, which is very important. 

発話者3  (33:26)
Then, you have an introduction of the manual planner for our patients, your case would be whatever planet your business kind of planet, and it will plant breaks down the questions into smaller plants. For the suitcase, but it's not a container when you put a bunch trying to steer steer the lmp. Because what's going to happen is going to go around the world, typically, and let's put out this as you start to navigate on this case. 

発話者3  (33:54)
I have renewed on the lab. And I have sentiment and adoption on the right. But if I go and zoom out one of them on the left hand side and have a fire architecture that has a planet executed inside that so it decomposes a suitcase and goes into it. 

発話者3  (34:12)
Let me give you a little bit more detail. That's zooming on the supervisor here's a question that a typical reduced person access to. Hey, can you give me what are my top 10 customers by htr? 

発話者3  (34:25)
For the few one fiscal military assets that have all, which is a product of ours could be a switch or a ruffle or something. Along with the sentimental, it's a very detailable question. And a lot of comments on it. 

発話者3  (34:39)
So the fourth thing that we realize does happening to supervise the multiform condition is not enough. First thing that we need to have to supervise the dynamically generated is a notion of acronym is a liquidity. So what does H Tr ease on dichotomy at? 

発話者3  (34:54)
I is here means available to renews when it then means something else from a different conference that has basically said, and you start to go for this in that supervisor actually dynamically creates a plan on this case, it realized that after the seasonal tweak. What HDR means it realized? Oh, I have stage one that is reduced. 

発話者3  (35:17)
Stage 2 sentiment, one independent of one another, so it actually creates that plant. It's what the sugar agent needs to go and what the cortex needs to deteriorate. And then it's going to point down on this case. 

発話者3  (35:31)
For that equal part from what everyone uses Vs they offer 2 parts if I go through that in order to elaborate craft with the plant, we use the same execution with land draft and then give it everything is okay. You summarize the land graph and go to the number supply. If it's not, you need to reduce replaced and automate the graph, this is all time, and that's the Duo you don't need to qualify anything because in production at 1160, you at the same time. 

発話者3  (36:05)
You just don't know. So if I go deeper, it goes now to the planet so that when heat here on that state on the produce of my left hand size, the slide the same would apply for sentiment adoption. But let's focus for one. 

発話者3  (36:22)
If you look at this when you get to this supervisor that hits one of the tasks I have 2 shots, the examples, but we think that sutra I have now reduced the specific planet. So it's like a supervisor might set the proof that applies just for that agent because we think that agents that are super test that needs to have given a time. Remember the question that asked about it? 

発話者3  (36:51)
He wants this going in 26, there's no way the evidence knows how the fiscal year or Cisco runs for which months for which months, which support water is going to be different for the company, right, so we need to go from there and there's a lot of tasks that decompose so we think that agent was supposed to be a monolith of an agent. Now we open up and you have a planary service and that planet is going to define how we plan for suit patients within that context, and if you hit on the bottom, you have a reflection reflect is that stage to the scratch? 

発話者3  (37:25)
Okay, if you ask it gets out, go to the loop of a supervisor that has its own reflection require, if not, it's going to be until it gets to the threshold inside this. So he realize that the evolution of how we make things more skill, there's massive scale and unparalleled execution, and by doing so, you can evade and help me with one of the content, but as you go to the supervisor and returner, give a question implies multiple stages and the reflection requirement will be triggered to underwriting site, or after a supervisor act, over time, why shall you do this with you? 

発話者3  (38:07)
Because as we start to get more complacent about the question or more input for something like the landscapes that give you more complex, you don't have architecture or scale like this, you're going to have a lot of other cities and a lot of areas so by doing things, how important it is how important we use The Domain specifically subtracts, and you have a workflow aging that needs to be improved here and that is a challenge that we face that we address in a different way, which is, if I build a planet, let's say, a few Sharks on the supervisor all of these steps. 

発話者3  (38:44)
We all know other names for stunning and affordable musical process. No time is going to get before then, you're going to get percentage. He's going to inspire to you and he's going to act in a debate and environmental, I'll find myself. 

発話者3  (39:00)
So I can't just prove this. Let's not even go there when you go on a determinist between what it did actually adopted. The notion like all the coordination tools text like the quote code and cortex and cursor so we create a\\, then we actually create standard gas that are very big for what needs to run behind the things on every coup at the moment when he said, show me the top 5 review stuff that happened. 

発話者3  (39:30)
And if there was a catastrophic hours that happens overnight, tell me as well, and if it affects the sentiment brightness and things every morning. So don't think about it, just run what I'm trying to do, so what it is the greatest\\, like. If you go to quality\\like model, it gives you the options of the models to choose, it doesn't opinion, it gives you beliefs. 

発話者3  (39:56)
That's it. If you go and see it, give the np the same thing. So Think about nuclear business producers. 

発話者3  (40:06)
We find those ubio to the model most likely it's going to ask me, hey, I don't understand how the business brand teach me how old criteria for the behavior but if I go and put it, you impose, which is something we run on our business. Oh, boy, the resident is going to be all voluntarily sensitive to postpons. How you should be a friend? 

発話者3  (40:29)
Just do what needs to be done. So in the product, we have workflows that are determined this past race. So there's this program actually done that is not Helen involved. 

発話者3  (40:40)
And recently involved on debt, because I want them to follow the structure in the way there is because that's not all the risk everything else on the planet. We plan and all that those One last thing I want to talk about last thing we talk about object foundation. We have 95% accuracy. 

発話者3  (40:59)
A lot of users from burnt. Many carries a month all the right things. But then one thing happened. 

発話者3  (41:06)
We act Africans in thousands adoption closely plateau, a lot of people used trying to focus and then take those students, then we are scratching the hair, don't have enough hair to use by scratching it too like what the actual happiness, why the contact and they don't contact right and they come back to the stretch, until I have 2 really little, so we start to figure out so the first thing that I will share with all of you. For briefly, there is a notion of optionality. David renewation photograph was yes. 

発話者3  (41:43)
The model 2 It was not embedded on the workflow and tasked them daily jobs, so they had an option to see this. But by the human nature of the laziness of the almost opinions, they use things just for information and go and work back where they come from. So we work on a concert residency. 

発話者3  (42:06)
That's called 4 step curiosity with a management to actually get them. There and at the same time, consolidate intelligence and the second thing he was actually informed to the teammates, so I need to get out of the stats on him to get basis a collaborator at homey. And for that, in effort, he need to be personalized, which led to us focused on everything that is AI. 

発話者3  (42:28)
Integrated folks why FBI expenditures reduce the whole cx organization and give some interesting for you that in working on this. Now, until now or 2, before software helps humans together more strong, our mindset, humans help suffer together, and the reason is because they stop asking the question. How can AI improve existing software for sensor approach to ask? 

発話者3  (42:58)
Is that work even and if I want to soften that software today, why? Because we are thinking about evolving for what the AI is used for assistance to AI to commit to results. Black mixture results include it on such a way that you stand on hand we step phase one typically have work phones work that one needs to step 2 is starting to be very sequential, to get AI execution and authority that instead of focusing a workroom logic, we focus on the confidence that the complex allow parallelization. 

発話者3  (43:34)
Is such a way that we give autonomy? By default, the whole world is alike building for exhibition and it only stops death. There is no confidence force which is complete, as opposed to ordinating with AI. 

発話者3  (43:48)
Every step which is always important so the humans after the confidence is always triggered, is not jumping for judgment as opposed to what is today when the judge the workforce has human DNA. Human handle orchestration, by DNA on how many observation the people that are asking to change is the same people? Hey David remember this so describe some resistance I'm just studying it so some notes around here that not things that we would that allow us to revolt for the Chatbot to our teammates and dedication targets authentic systems. 

発話者3  (44:31)
Our highlight, the monster memory, is a lot of mention contributions of that. Especially tests all the shortcuts that we mentioned and making intelligence drive. And let's put not least use some of the lessons from it. 

発話者3  (44:46)
I'll take the rest of them in 2 members, one. That's system itself accuracy, stable space. So we have a magnify the percent accuracy, we believe that was enough, he wasn't stabil state. 

発話者3  (44:59)
We need to give patients and personalization for adoption, move. Past chat is just one surface in creators. We can, with the workflows discovery task, the available elevation, the whole body yards, which makes adoption and loses much better make people personal. 

発話者3  (45:15)
Why that is make the system and document user, not our liver, not trying to see producers, just because the system needs that function, the mindset, then and dedicate for DNA to actually something that you define how you handle things in the aircraft. I actually won't put our team, I said, hey, this is enough for the long last amount of how the system works, but there is enough layer which is the agenty infrastructure. How is it? 

発話者3  (45:45)
I'm used to this all the things I was showing you start focusing. Then explain why I meet by that. Let the agent help. 

発話者3  (45:55)
You before you're letting packs. So what I notified that the reason inequality not necessarily is there for all the things that how we end up with work for predictive workflow, it's deterministic, because everything was a piece of graph that so like use one is grouped for before the medical web stereotype self function is not optional, the difference between a pilot and a production is when you have. This actually calculation fits its own out on a wave that also opportunities and low range. 

発話者3  (46:26)
We better talk more tomorrow and we saw them, push both indeed, on that. And the last show here is quite tins of Frank and platinum swimming is something in which investment acknowledge up front, including for the models presented as a new, and most smart model, is going to solve the problem is a policy. Don't think about that. 

発話者3  (46:47)
The model is a healthy word. Don't chase benchmarks unless but not me. So liquidity routine is your first precision before you take action. 

発話者3  (46:57)
The, if you think about how the release the next discovery, because that processification is hard, then without doing this the models you will listen to, because they don't know with that said, I hope it's helpful and show you how we evolve in one year. And how much in our year take never change. Thank you very, very much. 
