
発話者1  (00:04)
Hey Bixby 

発話者2  (00:07)
It's raised for us, so we breathe so it doesn't mean A harnessed with memory memory is a context context becomes a plan. So it acts but action So we observed measuring personalized and improved improvement again. Tests evaluate deploys picks again faster tests evaluate deploy. 

発話者2  (01:05)
It's not just intelligence It is a lie. 

発話者2  (01:20)
The stage parasitic and CB 

発話者1  (01:22)
No quantum. 

発話者1  (01:41)
I have decided. I did not know that video was gonna be made. So We're not excited to be here, and this is our second year doing it. 

発話者1  (01:56)
And so we decided to get 2 names instead of one and we've got a stacked lineup for everyone here, I think it's going to be a last. We've got a lot to share, and so we're thrilled and honored that you guys decided going for these 2 days last year, we kicked off interrupts by talking about a building agent was hard. It was easy to build a prototype but it was hard to get the production. 

発話者1  (02:19)
There was a lot of challenges that encountered along the way and over the past year, we've seen that a number of companies, including a lot that are speaking here today, have figured out how to overcome those hurdles and bring agents into production. So not easy to build agents and romantic corruption, but we've figured out some of the things that are needed to make better reality. Building agents is different than building software. 

発話者1  (02:46)
That's why it's new channels. That's why new tools and new skills. And I think it's important to think about why it's different than building software. 

発話者1  (02:57)
There's two things that we think make it different. One is the inputs themselves. So agents take in natural language, natural language and the infinite institutions. 

発話者1  (03:06)
It can be any number of words or now things can start to be images or videos or even audiophiles and so that the input space, the agents is really, really large. The output space is also really large albums themselves are non deterministic, and even if they were deterministic, they're still really sensitive small changes in the front. And so we have this really big input space, and this really non robust system, you end up with an overall adventurous system that's really hard to actually predict how it's going to do before you actually launch it. 

発話者1  (03:41)
And you actually put it in front of the users, and you actually have them, experience it. And the teams that have figured out how to build a news reliably, they ship early And then they iterate quickly, and this is a pattern that we've seen again and again, from companies that have managed during agents in production. I think you this generation. 

発話者1  (04:04)
Through some mayor they've landed on this new agent development life cycle. Parallel to the software development, life cycle that people use the building ship software, but it's different as agents are different. They require more iteration and the steps at each of those phases are slightly different. 

発話者1  (04:22)
And so the mastery of this life cycle, whether people call it, that or not is really what people are doing when they're building organizations and building tools to help shape them and everything that we do at linking, can be described by fitting in this life cycle, we want to figure out what the agents of this. Future look like, and we want to build all the tools to help make them a reality. And so we think a lot about what this life cycle looks like, and how we can help that And today I want to talk about how we view this web cycle and I want to talk about a number of things that we are launching to make it easier for teams to iterate quickly through this life cycle. 

発話者1  (05:02)
So first I want to talk about bill building agents. This is how we got started. This is what lancain was. 

発話者1  (05:08)
This was a package launched in a month before chat GP. T and it was really around building these outlaw and antigenic applications. Fun fact, we had a class called agent in linking 4 types of nuance. 

発話者1  (05:21)
I remember time that was on. I think I've seen San Diego for Thanksgiving and trying to decide what to call it and I ended up calling it agentian executive, instead of agent. So you know, we're not great at any. 

発話者1  (05:32)
And that's maybe the first example of that, but we have this concept of an agent and we did lanking. Then, we launched Lane graft a little over a year later, as we saw that the applications that people were building, they may have started off this screens, but they were becoming more complex graphs. And that was the idea behind lengraph. 

発話者1  (05:54)
We got launched playstream wandao and then about 9 months ago, we launched tea papers. Teeth papers is an evolution of this as well, and so I want to talk a little bit more about beef havens right now because that's where we think the future is really headed. So the core Academy from the original agent executive blank chain is now is basically it's pretty simple. 

発話者1  (06:17)
It's not one run running in a loop calling pools, there's a bunch of stuff that can happen around that loop. There's a bunch of specific tools. You can add in, but when people talk about nature, this is essentially what they're talking about. 

発話者1  (06:28)
But user requests comes in, you call the LLM. The LLM decides to call a tool. You then execute that tool and keep on doing that, until the LLM decides that it's going to cut the core idea of the nation, and that's always been the case. 

発話者1  (06:41)
So what is behaviorals? Behaviors is an agent harness, and it basically adds for batteries included things that supercharges the loop. What are the sum of the things that it has? 

発話者1  (06:53)
Hey, bass and execution environment. So Adam harness is meet a place for rock, a really popular way for one. Then, is in a sandbox to give it access to a file system. 

発話者1  (07:04)
Give it access to code. It can be filed right files. Recode, that's just execution environment, and so when people talk about each harnesses, they often talk about cooking instruments and a key part of that cooking agent. 

発話者1  (07:15)
Is this execution environment? Sandboxes are what extreme you can write at an executive code, and then, on the other extreme, we have what we call virtual cloud system behaviors. This is basically a database that we expose to the agent as a phyloge. 

発話者1  (07:31)
System llms are great at reading and writing files, and so you can kind of trick it into having this kind of like mock execution environment, but the point is you've given an environment to interact with. Deep agents and other agency cars has come off a lot of built-in contact management. So skills and memory are examples of best summarization is an example of short-term memory. 

発話者1  (07:55)
When conversation gets wrong, you summarize it context offload you, how do you deal with, like, really long pool calls? This is logic that's built-in that the agent harness From fashion is another example of this where you want to make sure that your passion, the initial part of your request so that it can be faster and cheaper in the future. So all this context management is built into the artist and it does it automatically for you. 

発話者1  (08:20)
Steering is really important. So these agents, these key agents, the long horizon agents, but that doesn't mean they're fully autonomous these films and the loop. And so, deep agents comes with a really good human loop controls And the last few delegations agent harnesses can be used to kick off other agents, whether that's planning agents or other sub agents for different tasks. 

発話者1  (08:40)
And so all of that delegation communicating with the subagents and having them communicate back to you all that is specified in major hardness. And so keep paintings contains all of these different things. We spend a ton of time doing both research and applied AI work to make sure that the way we do summarization is the best, the way that we do something is the best. 

発話者1  (09:03)
And so today, one of the things that we're launching is deep agent 0.6 a new version of deep agents. There's 3 big things in it that are informed by free trends that we see in the industry. So once your NBC in the industry is the rise of open models. 

発話者1  (09:22)
Do you see before launch last week? And stress this performance uncertain past as frontier models. So open source models are getting better and the other thing that's happening is cost is rest. 

発話者1  (09:36)
The cost of frontier models keeps ongoing up-and-up. They usage keeps ongoing up-and-up. And so one of the things that we think will happen more and more is more usage of open source models. 

発話者1  (09:46)
And so if 0.6, we want to admit the best place, use open source models, throw onto native support for Yale and 5 deep sea Indian models. We have the best inbox integrations with inference Partners like fireworks, Facetime and NVIDIA. I'm the easiest way to try out. 

発話者1  (10:06)
Open source models in a harness is by Kobe and so we're launching deficits code as an open source example of how to build a COVID agent on top of these agents. And we're making a really, really good for open source models. The second thing that we're seeing is a lot of attention around the execution environment. 

発話者1  (10:25)
So we talk about this. We talk about the virtual file system which is a really simple way to let the agent interact with what it thinks. The file system is just a presimple database under the hood. 

発話者1  (10:34)
And then, on the other extreme, the full one's code sandbox, where they didn't write. It has a good code spin on the web server. Any of that And so, this is the spectrum The Web sits in the middle And so eBay became 0.6 raw launching coded interpreter. 

発話者1  (10:50)
What code interpreter is we use quick J? S which is a job strip runtime, and it basically lets the agent write and execute code in this kind of like grapple like environment. So in the software, the jobs work language and you can't do everything that you can do in a sandbox. 

発話者1  (11:08)
So you can't run doctors, things like that. But you can still write and call tools programmatically, you can manipulate data files. You can read and write from the file system here as well. 

発話者1  (11:17)
And so we think this is a really interesting, middle ground where super lightweights deploy, so this is the benefit of that, you don't have to spin-off the separate standoffs for YouTube, you can just deploy this. And it's really easy to run in a multi time way, but you still get a lot of benefits that you get from COVID. The third trend that we've seen is that it still really are. 

発話者1  (11:39)
But really important to build delightful bodies, pattern, interactive scenes, patterns, and something that's happened. Is these agents have done a more and more complicated, and the events that they're living are corresponding to more and more complicated? They admit texts, they admit Google calls. 

発話者1  (11:53)
Images, these names sometimes stop having to do that. And so what we want to think is easy as possible for people around the Asian harnesses and hook them up to the lightful office that they built for their customers. And so the third watch in deep agents,0.6 is better support for streaming. 

発話者1  (12:11)
So we have a brand new screen protocol. We have four different front SUVs for different front end languages, and we're partnering with UI frameworks, like copilot fit assistant UI and vercell to make sure it's really tightly integrated. Do eyes are a big part of building agents and we want to make it the easiest way to do something. 

発話者1  (12:32)
So if you haven't already tried out these agents, please go try it out today. This is where we think the future is having. These engagement harnesses are getting more and more robust, more and more production ready. 

発話者1  (12:41)
And these agents, these are version of that I want to talk about the test phase next, so you've built your agent. How do you know if it's actually working? This is where lengthsmith evaluations, content, something we've been building over the past few years. 

発話者1  (12:59)
Testing for agents looks different than testing for software. You want to build up Datasets so referenced models and reference outputs for many criteria as a score. I was doing You wanted to find aspects. 

発話者1  (13:12)
How do you know if the capacity this could be carefulness? This would be hallucinations, but you wanted to find some metrics that work for your use case. And then you run your original state assets and you score them on these metrics. 

発話者1  (13:23)
And you create these experiments, and you can use these experiments to help climb on certain things, or you can use them to make sure that you're not regressing that you're making changes. A valuations are a key part of blank Smith, and we're launching some stuff around us today. But I'm going to talk about that later. 

発話者1  (13:41)
So I'm gonna go on to deploy that's So you've built period it's running locally now you want to go to production. There's a bunch of challenges that are going to do that. First, you have to go from a single user, just to you. 

発話者1  (13:52)
Now you're serving money in production environment, variables and memory. These now have to be specific to users that you're interacting with off, you can control masks that you can't just open it up to everyone. And then, when the brands locally and it dies, you know, your testimony can resume from there. 

発話者1  (14:10)
But you need to run it duratively when you run into that scale. And so a year ago, we launched lengths of deployments to help with this. So there's a bunch of features built into this. 

発話者1  (14:19)
We launched about 30 different abi endpoints to handle streaming Human in the loop. All Other things like that is a single standard employment pattern. Today, it serves over a 100 million human rights and is trusted by companies like workday, Cisco. 

発話者1  (14:34)
Et. Ce podium and bytedance. But we also realized that Lacey's appointment isn't the only thing you'll need to bring engage into production. 

発話者1  (14:45)
We've talked about how agents need an execution environment, and one of the best execution environments is a sandbox. So, whether the agent is a cooking agent or not. Reading and writing code can be really impactful for the agent to manipulate data. 

発話者1  (14:59)
That way examined it and use clis that way, and so we generally think that a lot of agents when we need the ability to fragment. And so today, we're excited to announce that links to sandboxes is generally available We think this is a big part of the issue in the future. And so we made it really easy to spin out sandboxes. 

発話者1  (15:23)
In less than a second. There's for assistance for these sandboxes, so that will survive across interactions this support, snapshots and force, one of the coolest things we've done. Is this off proxy says you want to give the album? 

発話者1  (15:36)
The agent, the ability to do something that requires an IP actually wanted to see that API. Because then if you get promptly injected and leaked it and so we have an off proxy that sits outside the sandbox and basically use recepts traffic and inserts that in. And this is all part of the length. 

発話者1  (15:51)
It's completely free working off, so you can use it to keep it in. You can use it without a contagion. You can use it for testing agents. 

発話者1  (15:57)
You can use it for rl, you can use it for running agents for production. We're really excited to see how people use it. So we've already had a number of customers using it Monday. 

発話者1  (16:06)
For example, uses it so their AI system side picks, and we're excited about we've gotten so far. I know that a big part of bringing agents. The production is context so albums by themselves that they don't know anything or they don't know anything. 

発話者1  (16:23)
Humans don't know everything when we even look up things we go to a library. We look at we look at books to learn things, we read them. And that's exactly what they need to do as well as context. 

発話者1  (16:32)
And that context has evolved over the years as album. So we had a conclusion in lane, SMEs for the longest time, where you can store inversion, prompts. And in terms of the things that kind of like guided agents, but over the past few months and 10 years ago, we've seen that the context provided that agents has graduated from prompts because things like agents got empty files. 

発話者1  (16:54)
So really detailed instructions and skills that these agents had used a lot of these shapes, like putting these standards. Both of these are open standards, by the way, so they're part of open foundations and so as the context that albums that have needed has evolved from prompts into these gains out of being skilled. So has our pulling for that. 

発話者1  (17:14)
So today, we're excited to launch playing Smith. Context stop And so what's in this context? So you can take your agents out of defiles, you can take your skills, you can take your like out along Wiki. 

発話者1  (17:32)
So this thing like our coffee did, where you basically ran in all one and had to generate Wikipedia, which are condensed knowledge in a markdown file using? That's going to become a more and more common pattern. So you can take all of this. 

発話者1  (17:43)
You can store it in context stuff. You get versioning, you get tags, you get comments, and then you can use it, you can pull them down locally, you can run them in your cooking cli and run them in deep agents as a virtual file system. So we have an integration there, or you can use them in whatever agent harness, you have. 

発話者1  (18:01)
We think context. However, is a first start at number. We think memory is really, really important to agents in this future. 

発話者1  (18:07)
We think agents that I need and skills. You can absolutely view those as in the early form of memory, those are open standards. So that's because there's a great thing because we think memory should be open, we think memory should not be locked in to analyze to a framework or to a platform. 

発話者1  (18:23)
And so even though we're building a context, we want this idea of context to be really open, and so we're working with a number of companies, including Reddit, has elastic mongo and pine film. To turn this first stab at memory into something that's an open standard for memory for agents within the end of this field. And last thing we've got modern, so you've launched it. 

発話者1  (18:51)
How do you know what the event is actually doing? This is where a lot of the core links with functionality around Tracy, so you can make sure that you can see the step of every agent in the invatar, what the outputs are dashboard so you can track costs and latency over time online details so you can run album as a judge for code over these traces, get some feedback and then patch up or just patch your view. Back all of this is part of a link in the durability within building a lot here, over the past few years, and over the past few months, we've got a few very big launches here that we're going to take that for a little bit later. 

発話者1  (19:28)
So this is the ancient development life cycle. And this is what makes this what it looks like. Bring agents and maintaining this introduction. 

発話者1  (19:35)
And when you do it once for an agent, that's fine, and you do it for 10 or when you do it for a 100 agents. That's when you really start to think about the governance of all this, how do you do this? At scale, have you used this in the cost, efficient insecure way, and so specifically 2 of the concerns that we've seen emerge around governance over the past months, have been costs and data exposure. 

発話者1  (19:55)
Lms are getting expensive. How do you know how much agents are spending? How much specific users are spending on agents? 

発話者1  (20:03)
And how do you avoid surprise bills on the data exposure side? How long is a great networking data, but they shouldn't be able to access every source of data? And so how do you control what they can and cannot seek Today, we're launching lanesmith album gateway in beta to help with that. 

発話者1  (20:27)
The destination is picking shoes, which surrounds me to clock. So what is lengths with all along gateway? So you've got your avents, they're running lengths with all the gateway, basically sits between them their Ulm calls. 

発話者1  (20:40)
You do set stud limits. You can have visibility called visibility Uber spend, and then you can also set guardrails to help with Pi and secret sections. It integrates with a bunch of protein agents out there so that you can use it and know that coating agents is the most popular thing that people are using, and that's where a lot of these costs are happening. 

発話者1  (20:58)
So we've made sure to animate it with a lot of putting us out there. It integrates with all the alarm required that lane change can help you access and everything's traced automatically. So this is the full agent development life cycle, everything that we're building, and is sits into this, and we recognize that there's a lot in here, but taking an agent and going to production and going through this life cycle involves a bunch of different pieces. 

発話者1  (21:24)
And so we want to make it as easy as possible for people to take all these pieces take these patients which had already been harnessed under the lung and really, really easily go to production and sort of make that into a single API today we're announcing in private preview management. So manage division is a single 8 guy for interacting with all these different components, so it runs the deviation harness under the hood. It's deployed with lambsmith deployments and so that's where the agent will run the models that you can access include any models out there. 

発話者1  (22:03)
So we obviously integrate with OpenAI and the profit but also with the open source model providers like fireworks and base 10. All of the ancient instructions and memory are stored in context. So that, as you order users or the agent itself, updates them, you can see them there and version them there and track them there. 

発話者1  (22:23)
These agents when they're deployed, you basically want to deploy the agent over here and they need an access to a standbox to run right people's over here and all those two separate things. So that's the architecture that we cover, and we use lens to the sandboxes to help power those sandboxes in the hood. Mces are how you connect them to tools, so you can provide mctps directly, or you have to use arcade or another partner that provides access to a lot of mct service to do that, and all of this screens out in the new screening protocol that we announced so you can integrate it super seamlessly with a pilot kit, assistant UI and other frameworks. 

発話者1  (22:57)
So combining that resentment chain, open source and language power, this whole agent development life cycle. And we think that traces sit at the center of this life cycle. And so we spent a lot of time as a company thinking about traces and thinking about how to build the best experience around them. 

発話者1  (23:17)
Everyone does. But there's no one at the company who thinks more about traces than Michael founder on He said to me for the past almost a year, around how we make the experience around traces the best possible experience. Because this is what powers that whole movement I'm sure we're watching a lot of really cool things around this, but in order to talk about traces and love of traces, I'd like to welcome onto the stage Michael power on this gown. 
