
発話者1  (00:00)
Alright, terrison, a picture of what the future of agents in the workforce will look like, I'm excited to tell you all we're actually doing that late change today. First, I'm just starting with you kaln. Acquisition team forces candidates using our sources meant for sales team automates outbound and Ital. 

発話者1  (00:20)
intelligence. But I go to market agents, our marketing team researchers intended landscape with our intelbod and our engineering teams, triage and fixed instance automatically with overseas. Across the company, occasions are constantly running. 

発話者1  (00:36)
Monitoring the business and providing real-time updates slap. One of all these agents have it own. Well, they were all built by the Lane chain team members who actually used them without having to write single line code code. 

発話者2  (00:51)
How do we do that? 

発話者1  (00:52)
Where are you else they use links took? Please? Our manage agent builder, which allows us anyone to build agents with just factor link. 

発話者1  (01:00)
It allowed to write any difficult The last 3 years, building agents, we've learned remained things one, the best people to build the agents are the ones who actually do the job, so agents need to work where you were, and have access the same systems. You And 3 axerated scale governance, and become a model So why is it that the best people to build agents are the ones who actually did the job? Well at the end of the day? 

発話者1  (01:35)
Agents are just a collection of instructions, skills and tools and grew best to qualify that when the people actually doing the job. Also, just like how all of us improve over time, lead agents do as well. They have memory to build directly into them. 

発話者1  (01:51)
So the more you use them, the better they become. Now, in order to work the production witness agents, they need to have access to all the systems you sold that room tools and channels we have over 200 tools built directly into police that cover the most common integrations, companies required. We also have the first class partnership with our ticket. 

発話者1  (02:15)
Allowing you to access extra 7500 tools out of the box cover the long tail of your integration requirements. Of course. We support everyone's favourite tool framework, mcponnect, your custom tools and proprietary data, sources directly of tools. 

発話者1  (02:34)
Now in order to use them easily easily, the agents are integrated daily slap female outlook and more. You can utilise the full power of leaf without having to learn to workflow. We also have any comprehensive user interface which you can use to build man it and drive your agents directly within our app. 

発話者1  (02:56)
And of course, having forgotten by developers out there, we're opening up to the guys, you can use them directly within your own production applications and harness all of the incredible features we build. So people work in teams, these agents need feel to work seamlessly alongside. How do we handle that sharing? 

発話者1  (03:18)
Of course. You can share and collaborate on your agent skills directly and leafs, just as easy as sharing off with your teeth. Could you actually go to give you these sorts of agents? 

発話者1  (03:29)
You need credentials and authentication managements when you connect to all your different services and this, if you really tricky. Buckley, we've solve this view, please meaning. You can connect all your accounts and fit. 

発話者1  (03:43)
Switch agents use which accounts depending on which user is using. I'm rush doing We've notice how pass the skyrocket. As your agents are adopted earlier for that leedfill, cost tracking and usage controls directly into the app. 

発話者1  (04:01)
So even inspect exactly how much your agents and users are spending and set spend limits on them. Human hallou is also first class feature in please. You can give your agents access to powerful tools without how it's worry, and of course, leat integrates data with the rest of the latest platform. 

発話者1  (04:22)
You can look at your agent traces and see exactly how your feet agents are operating under the hood. Finally, please open model agnostic. You can use your favourite open or closed force models. 

発話者1  (04:36)
It's built on top of everyone's favourite, open source agent artists, guess that keep agents and we make it ease for you to download your agent files directly into your code. You can make whatever modification you would like. Now you can hand it off the paralines, where you give us a live demo. 

発話者1  (04:54)
Did you heard that right live demove minutes? 

発話者2  (04:59)
Thanks through route. So we have So we've talked about why and some of its capabilities. And I'm excited to show you what that looks like, practise. 

発話者2  (05:14)
Okay. We have our gone of party. This agent can service account intelligence based on data from R CRM through calling platform and new data warehouse. 

発話者2  (05:24)
It can research accounts and it can draught personalise how vow In order to do that, we connected it to the tools that we use your election. So in our case that sales for speakery etc. We've written certain sub agents for common research tasks that we wanted to before, and we've given it a long list of skills for step-by-step destruction on a tasks that we wanted to get right every time. 

発話者2  (05:55)
We've also connected the sock channel. So instead of having to come to the UI fear in order to the agent, you can use it directly in spot by tagging at TM. Okay, enough said let's run here we go. 

発話者2  (06:12)
Winning these things offer the pie tighter account. What's our next steps team? As it runs, this field market agent has been a game champerity. 

発話者2  (06:23)
The go to market key, 84% of the go to markets lead to qualify conversion is up 240%, and it has saved on average 40 hours per month for red Original engineer can felt the station direct But we don't see we rebuild this agent directly, so to go to markets, clean food own this agency, computation entirely Ed to end without having the right to single one. Okay, so the 80 plus wrapped up. We're seeing an at risk account. 

発話者2  (06:59)
That's not great square seize of hesitation. Around, right? And recommend it next steps to regate verified. 

発話者2  (07:08)
Now let's done Briefing immunology. As brace mention, human is first possible. So before we just send off the clean on to a potential customer, this agent is going to check-in with us so that we can double-check the coffee can make sure everything goes to before we said. 

発話者2  (07:30)
So let's take a look here. Let's optimal line play graph. Correctly, everything was stood. 

発話者2  (07:40)
Cool. Great, okay. Many of the agent. 

発話者2  (07:45)
Thank you. 

発話者1  (07:50)
He's ready. 

発話者2  (07:52)
Many of the agents that we use every day he're a light game are available as free built agents directly, so there's a go to market agent which you just saw, but also our software engineering, which allows fully units that you can tag and Puck, have a right code in a Sam boss and then put up a yard for universe. All you have to jury with. It is create the agent connected to the tools that your organisation uses and then go through a short onwarding flow. 

発話者2  (08:22)
So it gets to know your company and then you're good to go. And it was that I'm going to hand it back over to Harris. 
