
発話者1  (00:14)
I don't know about you guys, but this is the coolest at conference I've ever been to, and I've had nothing to do with it. So before we get started, I do want to shout out everyone who's working behind the scenes. In particular, Jess Julia Jacobs and Brianna, after making this as unfantastic. 

発話者1  (00:28)
So let's give them a big round. Now, yesterday we talked a lot about what building agents today looks like and how a lot of the most successful teams are bringing agents in production. And so for today, I want to talk a little bit about the future. 

発話者1  (00:49)
One of the things that we think a lot about at language, and it's actually in our mission and visual statement is what are the agents of future look like. And so for the rest of this talk, I want to pretend like we're a year in the future. It's interrupt 2027, and what are the topics that we're going to be talking about? 

発話者1  (01:07)
What are the topics we're going to be discussing and I'm going to be wrong in a lot of these going to look really silly and really stupid, but hopefully this gives you a glimpse into where we think the space in the industry is going One thing that I think will start happen is there will be a divergence in types of in the types of agents that people are building. So I think there'll be 2 types of agents who are already starting to see some of some So one of the types, I think, will be these long horizon style legumes. 

発話者1  (01:37)
So these are agents that run for minutes and hours, maybe even in the future days, they do code execution, they do planning, they do stuff agents. They need to use post agent systems. They use skills and they operate over longer and longer time. 

発話者1  (01:51)
Horizons, things like outcomes and goals are starting to become ways to increase the horizons at which we can operate. And so I think we'll see a big push and need as they do more and more valuable knowledge work at the same time. There's a completely different set of agents that latency is a huge factor for and these often end up looking like customer experience agents. 

発話者1  (02:15)
So this could be customer support be sales. This is places when you're talking to a net user brand is really important. Here voice becomes a really interesting modality. 

発話者1  (02:24)
Maybe video wealth in the future as well. And so I think these are these 2 directions that agents are going in. There is a shared underneath. 

発話者1  (02:34)
There are also differences in terms of the technology and I think one of the big questions that we'll be thinking about over the next year is how common is this shared staff Vs how particular are the technology pieces that you need for you? Speaking of voice, I think we'll be talking a lot more about voice in a year. This is a place where we're starting to invest more and more. 

発話者1  (02:56)
We see this be particularly relevant to these customer experience style regions and voices of great modality. The typical voice pipeline today looks something like this. There's a speech text, a speech kind of like sandwich. 

発話者1  (03:11)
So the user speaks that's transcribed into text that's passed to an agent. The agent operates in kind of like the text space outputs some text, and then that text is transformed back into speech, which is the audio that you hear at the agent as you're talking to them. And so this is the pipeline that we see today, but there are these native speech, native voice models that are coming out. 

発話者1  (03:34)
So OpenAI released me 2 of their is I think two weeks ago, and while I would say the consensus today seems to be for applications where you really care about having control, they're not quite serable enough yet we do accept that the change. And so I think one of the big things that we're looking at in the future for voice agents is which will be this pipeline approach. Will it be this needed voice to voice approach? 

発話者1  (03:58)
Will it be a combination? What are the pros? What are the con I think we'll be talking a lot more about voice in the next year or so? 

発話者1  (04:06)
We think all the events will leave a sandbox. Especially in these long horizon style legends so coding is really good for a variety of packes, not just writing software. It's for data analysis for web browsing. 

発話者1  (04:16)
It's for image genes for deep research. I was talking to someone yesterday who said that when they think about building agents for their marketing team, one of the ways that they think about it is they think about giving that marketing team a software engineer, what would that software engineer build what apps would it build to make the marketing team's job easier. That's what giving an agent the ability right next to code is that's why we think sandboxes are really important and that's why I launched sandboxes yesterday. 

発話者1  (04:42)
So we, I actually think agents are very early on. Sandboxes are very, very early on. It's still just a dawn of those. 

発話者1  (04:49)
I think will be talking a lot about them over the next year right now, right? Open models are a place that we expect to see significant increase in over the next year. So the performance of these base open models, without any type of post training for particular tasks is already approaching that of care models. 

発話者1  (05:08)
So this is some benchmarking that we did on deep, comparing, closed frontier models to open models. And you can see that it does last in some places, but it's starting to get really, really close to that frontier. The other big thing that is happening is cost is starting to become more and more of an issue. 

発話者1  (05:26)
So there are multiple cases where in particular for coding agents, these agents are firming through a ton of tokens really, really fast, I think open models offer a cheap alternative to these, and we expect that that would be a big driver of open models. A third reason that we think open models are really interesting is because they can be trained for your particular domain. And so I think that's yet another reason that, as companies build up a lot of these trace, a lot of these Asian garages, how can you use those? 

発話者1  (05:56)
How can you use those to improve the model? Over time? I'll talk a little bit more about that in a second. 

発話者1  (06:00)
But this type of poached training is something that you can do with open models, and so we expect a big rise in terms of open models. Agent identity is really, really interesting to us. So as agents start to do more work in the real world, they take actions. 

発話者1  (06:16)
How do they take those actions on whose behalf do they take those actions? I think is still early here. We see 2 emerging trends. 

発話者1  (06:22)
One is when the agents act on behalf of individual users. So I'm accessing an agent and that agent has access to slack. And I tell it to look up something in slack that will use my credentials and we'll have access to whatever I see and slap. 

発話者1  (06:35)
So if Julia or her colleagues, they might get a different answer, because they might see different things. Another type of off is when they have a thick set of credentials. Usually a service account or something like that. 

発話者1  (06:47)
And then whoever is interacting with that agent, they will always use that fix set of credentials to go see the same responses. This, I think started to get really, really popular with things like open cloth where you had this concept of an agent that was its own thing. And it had its own fixed credentials, and you could expose it three separate channels and you'd interact with it, and we started to see, actually some past providers make it really easy for agents to create their own accounts. 

発話者1  (07:11)
So that they could have their own fixed set of credentials. And so I think this would be an interesting and trying to watch, I actually think we'll see both of these in the future. I think we'll have agents that act on behalf of users but also agents of their own fix that credentials, and I think the really, really precise about when to use which one and which ones which one is making that their users will be important. 

発話者1  (07:34)
Continual learning is maybe one of the areas that we're most excited about as a company. So when we set in about continual learning, we think about improving the objective system over time. And there's 3 layers to this adjunctive system, and all of them can be improved. 

発話者1  (07:49)
There's the model layer, there's the harness layer. And there's the complex layer, so the model things like sonnet, go on 5 harness, this is code surrounding them all that connects it to the environment, evasions, block code pie, and then context might be what we provide the rna as ways to guide it on particular tasks. So agent and the skills you can't edit plot code directly, but you can give it skills and give it an interest on D that tunes it for your particular task. 

発話者1  (08:18)
So these are three different layers of the adventure system, and we think all of them are involved in continual learning. So maybe starting at the model, there first is taken from research done by ramp prime intellect that came out last week. Where they find between the models to be really good at ramp sheets, and you can see here that the latency is very, very low. 

発話者1  (08:39)
And the accuracy is very, very high, and this is an advantage of using an open source model from 3.5 and a fine 2 units for their particular domain. And so this is an example of continual learning at the model. You can also learn at the harness level. 

発話者1  (08:56)
So there's a great paper out of mit in Stanford called Meta harness where they used an agent to optimize a Cody harness, they optimized it on terminal bench 2, and you can see that it outperforms human written harnesses, and so this is an example where they use the feedback from the environment, the feedback from running on terminal eventually cooked that feedback. They passed it through an adjunctive system itself that would make edits to the harness. So it wasn't changing the model at all, it just had editing the harness. 

発話者1  (09:23)
And they go to really good sport that My backgrounds in classical machine learning, and there's a lot of similarities between how you use data there and how you use it in this new world of Asian development and so in classical machine learning, you have the model, you have the training data you do some gradient descends and that updates the weights of the model, when you're updating the agent in general, depending on where you're at working out the harness or context layer, it's not exactly really detected, but the eles that you write act as a forcing function, so that the example of the metaphors that I just gave you have, these valuations terminal. 

発話者1  (10:02)
Density, you run the agent of terminal vent, you get something back. You then pass that into the adjective system and updates it. So there's these vowels are providing a similar type of this training gradient. 

発話者1  (10:14)
And so evals and traces are incredibly important for this learning. We did this ourselves, and so this is the this is a few months old at this point. And so all these, you know, the leaderboard no longer looks like this base moves really fast. 

発話者1  (10:28)
But we move from top 30 on terminal bench, 2 to top 5, just by changing the harness itself. So no changes to the model, only changes to the harness, and we saw a big increase in performance. And so we think that more and more companies will be doing this type of continual learning, whether it's at the model layer, the harness layer, the context layer for their particular use cases. 

発話者1  (10:49)
We want to help people do this. And so one of the things that we're announcing today is Lang Chang labs, which will be a research group inside of Lang chain aimed in particular, at cartinal learning, we think that again We think that lanesmith, which, with all these traces already in marille feedback so timing that this is a really, really solid foundation for doing this type of continual wedding, whether it's at the model layer or the harness layer or the context layer. And so we're excited to work with a bunch of our customers going forward in this direction. 

発話者1  (11:26)
The last thing that I'll say is we think that everyone will help build agents in this future and we already see this today. So we already see that everyone in the north is involved in improving the agent with feedback. So you've got less research, earnings, domain, specialists, customer support, folks, product people engineers that are all going to feed back in some form, whether direct feedback or by tweaking the prompts or by just debugging and slack, they're all getting feedback that improves these agents and oftentimes it's The Domain. 

発話者1  (11:53)
Experts themselves who have the type of feedback and know how the agent form best, and so we think in the future, there'll be even more involved in creating these agents. We think they're actually going to be building their agents, they're not just going to be giving feedback on them and handing that off to a separate team, they're actually giving me involved in building these agents. We've started to see a glimpse of this at length where we have a bunch of patients created by people in all different domains and expertise, and we've seen them build these over the past few months, and so to talk more about WhatsApp teacher looks like I want to welcome onto this. 

発話者1  (12:28)
Stage Caroline embrace. 

発話者1  (12:51)
All right, all right, everyone doing 
