
発話者1  (00:15)
Hey, everybody. We are super excited about the announcement and the launch of langsmith engineers. We really see this, as Harrison said in his keynote as the future of Asian observability and evaluation and of spinning this agent improvement, and what we want to do today is kind of walk you through the process by which we landed on what is now engine, and this cruel agent that runs on Lakeside. 

発話者1  (00:40)
And to start here at length Smith, where the agent engineering platforms. So as you might imagine, we'd love to build agents and we'd like to think that we're pretty good at. And internally, we have built a ton of them, including a go to market eater. 

発話者1  (00:58)
This go to market agent does account research for our good market team. It does account outreach for our customers as well. And as we were building and improving this agent, we saw a ton of different problems that we run into over and over the first being as we would be carefully and meticulously monitoring and observing what our agent was doing in the wild, we would still get inevitable requests from our own markets and say, hey, something is broken. 

発話者1  (01:23)
This didn't work as it should have even though we didn't moderate very closely. And for each one of those issues that would be product to us, the fix was oftentimes very straightforward, but tons of these very small fix start to add up, they get deprioritized etc. And with each one of these fixes, the process of creating good evolves to ensure that there aren't aggressions, guaranteed, and so oftentimes we find ourselves encountering these micro regressions and these are problems that as I talk to customers, I see all the time as our customers are building pages as well. 

発話者1  (01:56)
They are. Looking through their faces in a very manual way, which is extremely amphare Chrome. They are finding that a lot of these small spaces that they need for their agent to perform well are not getting prioritized. 

発話者1  (02:08)
Because there's so many viral things. And like Harrison said, and you know, this is feels like a game of whack mole, I'm going to fix one problem over here and another is gonna spring out because this process of created good email very difficult questions. And so what we wanted to build was an agent that would do this for us and resolve these different problems for us, something that would find our issues automatically for us, something that would fix those issues and something that would add testing to prevent against aggression. 

発話者1  (02:36)
And ideally something that would be doing this all the time so that our team could be focusing on expanding the functionality of the agent instead of fixing these irritating logs or errors. And what I'm excited for walking through is what we'll be landing on with lanesmith and I want to show you what that looks like in the U. R. 

発話者1  (02:54)
And so when Smith engines will identify errors from your phrases in your traces project and it will present them in this kind of prioritized inbox. 

発話者2  (03:02)
On the left 

発話者1  (03:03)
Each case, you have a nice description and a timeline that is occurring so I can see if this is something new or something that's been going on for a long time. And if I want to dive in deeper into any of these offending traces, I can actually just click into them right throughout the see exactly what might have occurred with the customer. And so I can kind of guide check because there's a real issue with some of the ideas. 

発話者1  (03:23)
Then, it goes beyond the addressing and the diagnosis of problems and actually works to fix those problems as well. But here you can see there's an adjustment to my prompt being proposed as well as an adjustment to one of my agent file. And if I want to open a pr right here in page, I could do so very easily. 

発話者1  (03:41)
The process of finding important problems is also very difficult and so engine creates custom online evaluators that are tailored to this exact problem. So that if it returns or recurs in any way, you can mimic The last part of this process that is so painful is the creation of data setting animals for your offline crowd and engine also makes it much easier by taking the error inputs that you've seen in production and creating a version of ground truth from each one of those examples so you can see here, I have the various inputs that I've seen in production. 

発話者1  (04:13)
The wrong outputs that have been generated by a customer and our earlier version of the agent and ideally what we'd like to see and this has created the assertion so we can advise data set or edit this in the meditation cue, if you have any concern, slow backgrounds like so really excited about the way that this connect and strings together all the different components of the at that age of engineering engines is an agent like we talked about. It pulls these different arrow traces, clusters them into issues. 

発話者1  (04:43)
For you. These are issues that you can action on very easily generates fixes for you and then works to improve your evaluation suite as well. Whether that's your online emails, whether that's your offline email. 

発話者1  (04:54)
Now, the version of anything that you just saw, as we were describing is working with a handful of our customers today, we have about 15 customers that are really awesome and are helping us to improve and make this version of engine, much better from clay to benta to campfire, they have given us really awesome feedback that engine is changing, not just the way that they interact with lengths, but the way that they are engineering, their agency entirely and is facilitating that process so much. But the product that they're using, that we just walked through is not where we first started with, and I want to talk to you about the earliest version of engine, if engines like this motor this powerhouse of that engine improvement loop, the first version was kind of like a wind up toy, and what we created was something that would take our length and traces automatically. 

発話者1  (05:44)
Send them to a coding. Agent, which would spin up pr. It would run on and GitHub action all the time and it was a little hacky but it worked and started the service different issues from our traces on our internal pieces. 

発話者1  (05:57)
And so, the very first PR that was created by this early version of engine was a real problem. It was some tool called that was failing silently, one of our agents and engine added some airplane for that. Not an insane fix by Eddie me, but it was a real problem that was addressed by the speed or so, we were excited about that, but more excited about the subsequent cases that we saw. 

発話者1  (06:20)
Here's another one for 1 of our internal agents that is an asynchronous coding that can be invoked via slap. And engine picks up that a lot of our users were requesting that the agent review the PR comments for the PR that had been created by the agent and this open squeeze the name of our coding agent would respond. I don't have that functionality. 

発話者1  (06:41)
I can't help you with this. And so engineer picked up on these users, getting these unsatisfactory responses and created this pr to extend functionality at, and this is getting really excited, feeling like this is not just going to find issues, but it's going to improve our agent. In all these different mentions. 

発話者1  (07:02)
Obviously this first version of engine needed some work, and one of the very first problems that we recognized with engine was that it was too good at finding the process it would oftentimes find travels that weren't R$, there's a Soviet era quote. Right. Show me the man and I'll show you the crime. 

発話者1  (07:24)
This is the guy who engineer was doing, who was finding crimes in all sorts of traces. Where there weren't any and What we quickly realized was that the process of finding and identifying real and meaningful issues and distilling those into actionable. Block it that we could work on was the most important part of the process. 

発話者1  (07:45)
The generation of the right kids and the generation of these vowels for afterwards, was definitely connected to the identification of meaningful errors. So a lot of our structural and architectural thinking was centered around this. How can we find good and employers? 

発話者1  (08:02)
Deputy involved an architecture. I want to just address something that I think is really incredible, which is that to power engines, and this agent we are using all sorts of blank chain products. Whether that's our deep agent framework that live works on, or whether that's our newly announced Santa boxes. 

発話者1  (08:19)
These are all power in this statement. Now, more into the week length engine is triggered from a whole set of different sources, an agent can kick it off at hot. But by default, it runs on a schedule whenever it's kicked off and triggered that kits are enlarged back. 

発話者1  (08:38)
That feeds into this multi tenant orchestration, with this distributed task queue that we have our license back, and that all feeds into a single landsmith deployment, that serves all of the different tenets, all of the agents that we have being improved by an engine, are all on the single length of the planet, where we have these 8 agents running and improving based on those traces. These invasions are pulling in traces and the source code of the agents that we're running on into a niceness of sandbox, one for each side. 

発話者1  (09:08)
And this process that you can see here, actually, is really just the process of identification. We decided early on that because of the massive context that are required to look through and investigate these different traces that it was better for us to split out the functionality from the identification of issues from the actual fixes of those issues. So you can see here. 

発話者1  (09:28)
There's this little section for fixes. Because it looks very identical to the graph that you're seeing, and it's just this urgent, specifically meant to create fixes. And attach those to the very feet that require so much this set of issues define, and each issue has a defined fix. 

発話者1  (09:46)
We service that to the user in the UI, and all of this, I'll note here all of this is being traced via length, and this is what we're using to understand how we're right now. Now, I've mentioned that the engine ingests traces of our user, and I just want to drive home to the point that Traces are far and away the most valuable input that our engine operators The code of your agent is valuable obviously, but it doesn't do a great job of telling how your agents form in the wild. There's a massive amount of non determinism when building with people and so the traces really are the window to the agent's soul. 

発話者1  (10:25)
And how it will perform from the wild. And so that is really what powers engine knowledge functionality Now we don't ingest the entirety of every single trace that is being traced on language, the power engine. Instead, we send it a condensed and summarized version of your trace. 

発話者1  (10:43)
And the agent has the ability to rash and investigate and look through more closely into those traces, looking for patterns that are interesting, where it might hold some kind of error. So now we also rely on our customers source code, right? That this can be optionally connected into and ended, so that we can more accurately diagnose spaces, as well as create these prs to very quickly address the problems that engineers serve. 

発話者1  (11:14)
But like I said, the traits are really what formed so much of what's powered. Now, when it comes to these actual faces that are proposed, sometimes these are small faces. Sometimes this is a minor prompted test. 

発話者1  (11:25)
Sometimes that's an adjustment to your skills, file or your agents and Lee file and many times it's an adjustment to the actual code of the agent's destruction. But what I feel really excited about is not just the actual code adjustment, but this contribution backed into your evaluation, whether that's creating online evaluators to text those problems that keep referring, or creating these regression examples. If you talk through during that memo that process of taking an input that you've seen in production with a bad or unsatisfactory output and creating a ground truth, deference, output very tedious today, and so really satisfied the way that engine proposes what ground truth might or should look like for those different things. 

発話者1  (12:05)
And then lastly, we want engine to work really well for our customers and for the different priorities that they have when we launch the first formal version of engine to that group of customers that I mentioned earlier, we saw that there was an important learning for us, which is that what's good for one of our customers. And one of our teams using anything might be very uninterestable to another team, we have a customer reach out to me early on saying, this is an organ. Great. 

発話者1  (12:32)
You guys are finding really awesome places where my economist, hallucination or leaking sense of the data, please stop showing me issues related to our context. Dean, bloated, we don't care our engines work at our agents working grateful. On the other hand we have customers saying it's awesome. 

発話者1  (12:49)
We're pointing out places where our cost is too high. Our lacency is way too high, and please stop showing us places for a hallucinating little bit. It's doing crime. 

発話者1  (12:58)
And so what we've learned is that for engines to work, well, engineering to work differently for the different teams that we are servicing. And so with that in mind, we've allowed for this improvement process, we're able to learn from our customers' behavior so whether that is changing the priority of an issue that is surfaced, whether that is ignoring an issue altogether, providing reasoning for why this doesn't matter to you or providing any other kind of natural language feedback that all feeds into what we call this agent coverage sounds like a memory file for engines, understand what you care about and how your agent So we're really excited about the process that we've undergone to improve engine and make this better for our customers. 

発話者1  (13:38)
We've been learning it very closely and we've been evaluating it very closely and to talk about the process of evaluating engines. I will pass it off through this. And it's 

発話者2  (13:54)
Amazon, now life then mentioned engine today did not look like engine four weeks ago. And the question that I really cared about is how do we know that engine is working. How do we know it's working today? 

発話者2  (14:07)
How do we know it's working four weeks ago, and how do we know it's going to work like 3 months from now? The answer to that question is of course, it's always about, so I'd like to mention engine. Does revamp this that identifies issue traces from a huge corpus of data? 

発話者2  (14:25)
It generates faces and a little bit evaluation, it creates eval, and for all of those things we need ebal, so we need evals for engines to create evaluations for you basically. How do we actually get those details? Well, the main way that we source them is from internal traces. 

発話者2  (14:45)
So like that mentioned, we turned the engine on for a background coding. For our G PM that gave us real user data, where the users for how this engine doing, how can we improve it? And that sort of kicked off this feedback cycle saying, okay, and this is not fact right here, but let's take those traces for them. 

発話者2  (15:04)
So all looting is a really, really good way if you are your own users, please check these out. The other thing is synthetic data, which is, let me ask an LLM to generate what it can develop. I've put human review in here in particular, because elephants are really smart, but they're actually very bad at this past, which we've got, which is generate a good amount. 

発話者2  (15:25)
They need a lot of 2 bricks and a lot of guidance and a lot of human review to be like, okay, this is a good year this is not And the third thing is we love to open community. A few dollars but what we found is that the best develop for our agent is one that's bespoke for our agent. So we use them to gut, check our emails, but we don't always use them directly to them. 

発話者2  (15:52)
Great. So we're getting the evasive wire, but how do we actually build a diverse and grounded app evoscula? So a trace and a short, it can be long. 

発話者2  (16:02)
It can be the finance of it can be medical domain. We want to have Els that basically capture that entire suite of data. The other thing is scenario is tasks. 

発話者2  (16:13)
So I might just want to measure how good an engine is at cost of the fuel. So the best way to do that is by making a targeted task that just measures that and I just said targeted tasks, and then I say N bank fast, because really what we found is the best way to measure engine is by putting in a representative set of traces and seeing highly antenna. And that allows us to do subpace optimization, like I said, let's just focus on this group, let's just focus on this problem. 

発話者2  (16:43)
Let's just focus on the skill that we found with it right. Let's just focus on those And how is how does detail 

発話者1  (16:51)
Form argument decisions. 

発話者2  (16:53)
Today every month we see a new autograph. There is 5474645, the fact that you'll all understand what those numbers mean is crazy. But everyone we have to look at what models we're picking back can be based on performance. 

発話者2  (17:08)
The cost latency and all of these are feedback signals that engineer takes in and can offer us suggestions for The other thing is complex engineering skill matters. Is fun? How should we design this tool? 

発話者2  (17:21)
If you don't want to put the 30 tools into the engine, we really design the engine, the autonomous and give it a minimal set of tools that it can perpetrate the self. And the last thing is, here is a blog that prompt engineering is death. Me and Ben did not find this to be true. 

発話者2  (17:35)
Prompt engineering is still very much alive, and sometimes the best way to actually code what your customers care about is by writing like very detailed things they can stop. And that's one thing we've found in our lifetime. And I just talked about, okay, I did this little rigorous process that I designed this develop, and I took feedback from this first step, but now I'm talking about the device. 

発話者2  (17:59)
I think there is a part of agent measurement that can't fully be captured by evals all the time, especially very early in our turkeys without having friendship. A big part of that was to include the product using it over and over again and getting feedback like that. And the first thing here that says, trust user feedback. 

発話者2  (18:18)
This is speech for us, usually at a customer, says, hey engines out of whack and R eval say that's not out of whack, it's probably out of whack and we need to update our eval suites to medical Now, this last slide is kind of the thing I'm most excited about as a research company. But it's the first part we're seeing of this self autonomous feature. So this is engine, which is an agent improving engine right? 

発話者2  (18:49)
Like, engine produces traces, just like any other agent, and we can take those traces. Ease them back into a version of engine and say, hey, how should we approve engine? Your context management isn't good, use a different model on finding these dishes, and that's what they're really centered about, have a bunch more share. 

発話者2  (19:07)
Soon but I will take it back to my brother's friends. 

発話者1  (19:12)
Is to summarize a couple of the key learnings and catalytic process, where I work for us defining that very crucial point of finding the importance and meaningful issues was really, really valuable for us, creating good products within that definition of the most crucial point in the flow I think is an important thing now, as a building in Italy. The other thing is that while we were building a we were very closely monitoring and understanding how was our agent performing under different scenarios, and that was all possible by using tools that we provided, especially And then I make this comment about the preferences of users that we allow. 

発話者1  (19:49)
And accommodate for online engagement, the truth is that engine was sort of saying real and accurate issues to our customers, and even from the accurate issues weren't always meaningful to them because they were misaligned at their priority. So the accommodation of this to make sure that our preferences are listened to by Andrew. There's a small face. 

発話者1  (20:07)
But made a huge difference, making engines not just that okay and functioning price, but something that really makes a huge difference for our customers. And then, lastly, as David has talked about this process of creating about super important filmmaking Canadian high quality valves, ultimately going to lead to high quality. We are really excited about the future of things. 

発話者1  (20:27)
Attention, we really feel like this is the future of lengthsmith, and the way that our customers are going to more easily have observability and create fixes and create their evaluations, and we're excited for that loop to spin faster and for to spend more autonomously Uber time, and we really can't for you guys cried out. Thank you. 
