
発話者1  (00:00)
We have these essentially create the best in class harness across these models. Now what we learned is that harness choices move benchmarks, meaningfully and so Harrison was talking about this today where we were, I think like 30th in terminal events, 2, we changed things to the harness. And then we got top 5, right, and of course, you know, that quickly gets replaced as the space moves really, really fast. 

発話者1  (00:24)
But the idea is that the hardest that you choose does matter, and it moves Ebel's significantly And then, lastly, right? Builders shouldn't have to forth deep agents because you want to use a certain model that you feel like the default harness doesn't do a good job at supporting. And so kind of just to show some emails on this concept of hardest profiles, so we ran some emails on a set of terminal events 2. 

発話者1  (00:50)
And we have 553 kodex, and we have caught opus 47 and we see that okay. Using this on a hard set of those problems, we got about 33% and 43%. But then, by using a custom profile, we can sort of increase the performance of our agent. 

発話者1  (01:06)
And so to give you guys an example of this right and why this is important is let's use OpenAI. So when OpenAI does post training on its model, right? It has a native apply,_patch tool. 

発話者1  (01:19)
That's what they use. We use and edit_file right? And so in order to get more sort of juice out of this model, let's use what it's used to, right. 

発話者1  (01:28)
Let's use what it learned when it's doing. Reinforcement learning right when it's doing post training. And so this is why it's important when we have a profile, we basically say, hey, instead of you know this us calling it, this read file tool. 

発話者1  (01:42)
Let's use this apply_patch right? So we're literally just changing, you know, you know, some words right? And just by changing some words, we improve the performance of our agent, which is just, you know, really, really interesting, right? 

発話者1  (01:56)
Like, these lms are quite finicky to text changes, and but this is an example of finicky that then actually ended up improving the result of deep agents with this custom profile. Okay, so we're talking about some of the components of deep agents. I really like to show this example of open suites, so open suite is this open software engineer that we have at lane shake, where I can just tag it and slack. 

発話者1  (02:22)
And it goes out, and it fixes a problem creates a pr. This is all built on defagents with sandbox, and so, you know, I think we talk a lot about like defagents here the different components of it, but I also want to show you guys like we actually use this. So we use this in a lot of places in our products, and one of those internally is for efficiency gains with our software engineers. 

発話者1  (02:41)
And so what you guys are seeing is in slap, Julian, our CEO has some feedback around the product and a software engineer is kind of working with her, and she's like, yep, let's try that and he goes, okay, sounds good. He tags at open suite, gives it some instructions for what it needs to do. It uses the repository, then it sends up a pr. 

発話者1  (03:01)
And now we can just go and review that pr instead of changing the workflow, right? Because all that context for what needs to be changed. Lives, right there in sla different parts of this product, right? 

発話者1  (03:12)
So we've announced lakesmith engine, right? And so length engine is an evasion under the hood, with different sub agents, and so we're using that in our products as well. NVIDIA is using deep agents, so they have this deep research that they use on top of deep agents in their open agent blueprint, and by using deep agents, they were able to get number one on deep research, benched leaderboards, and they did this at a lower cost with open models. 

発話者1  (03:40)
Again, one of the sort of visions, right? That Harrison talked about in his keynote. Is that open source models are going to get better? 

発話者1  (03:47)
And in certain use cases we can use open source models, and this is just the show. You like NVIDIA, did this, and they got number one, and they did it all with open bottles. All built on new patients Okay, so enough. 

発話者1  (04:00)
Just chatting about this. Let's go ahead and open up that notebook. It's okay if you don't have it installed, you can just follow along up here. 

発話者1  (04:06)
And we're gonna talk about different components of debates Let me go ahead and let me open it and then we'll go ahead and get started here. So let me scroll down. Let me just get some of these environment variables installed. 

発話者1  (04:19)
So for the sake of this, let's use gp 54 for the main agent I mentioned, you know, maybe we use a smaller model, cheaper model for the subasgent and so later on, we're gonna use gp 5 for a minute for that. So let's go down here. Let's talk about some of these different tools that you get out of the box. 

発話者1  (04:35)
So you guys are sure familiar with coding agents, right? And you see it with the use the ls tool, use the refille tool or write file tool. Maybe an edit file tool or glog or graph? 

発話者1  (04:46)
And so all those tools are natively with our agent harness at deep pages we have this planning tool so we can all write to news to keep track of tasks. If is it on track? We have this task tool that spins up sub agents, right? 

発話者1  (05:01)
And we'll add a subage, and we'll see that task tool in practice here, and then I mentioned like all these different context management pieces, including the auto eviction, the summarization of history, offloading of that. And then the other thing is, we have a ton of middleware that are built-in as well, which highly recommend is sort of take a look at that. So let's go ahead, let's invoke our deep agent. 

発話者1  (05:26)
The first thing that we're gonna do is just wanna show you guys that it can actually write and read files before we show that of writing and reading files using those native tools that I just talked about. Uh, I really want to make sure again that we come away this understanding with all these open source libraries of how they all stack on top of each other, and I think the best way to do that is actually look at the library itself and at the code. And so I highly recommend this is the same way I explain, like how they all fit into anyone. 

発話者1  (05:54)
That's sort of onboarding to lane chain, so let's go ahead. Let's command up into create deep agent. Let's go to the return statement and in the return statement. 

発話者1  (06:04)
So here we can see that we're gonna have this return, prey_agent and that comes from the lane chain library, right? So in the lane chain V1, we created this create_agent that is just the model running in the loop with tools. There's a model load of tools note, and you can configure that for however, you'd like, and what we realize is, people wanted this more like opinionated framework. 

発話者1  (06:28)
Right? Batteries included as kind of what we talk about. And so what are some of those batteries that we talk about? 

発話者1  (06:35)
So we have a default system like it's added into deep agents. The system rock is going to tell it a little bit about how to use those tools that we bring into deep agents obviously, if we are going to tell it, how to use those tools we need to make sure that we add those tools. And then, lastly, right we kind of talked about middleware, and there's a ton of mildware that's added in deep agents, so we need to configure that middleware as well. 

発話者1  (06:59)
And so again, you know, the deep agent function underneath the hood is just going to return and create agent create agent comes from lane, chain libraries. And then we go one level down. Let's click into create agent for those that are familiar with building with lane graph right? 

発話者1  (07:14)
You have this concept of adding nodes. I said that like agents writer models running and look with tools, and so I just have a model node and a tool node here and essentially, the agent can either call another tool or it maybe goes back to the user. And so if you guys are familiar like so that one, this is really really simple. 

発話者1  (07:33)
And if we're familiar with building what's running craft right? Maybe you created a long time ago, based on some constrictions of models, like 15 note architectures, but this is where we're converging, right? And this really simple pattern of just model running a loop with tools, but so this is laying graph, right? 

発話者1  (07:49)
This concept of nodes runtime, it allows for things like streaming and persistence human in the loop as well. And so again, this is how the creative major library stacks with the other open source libraries, where we have land graph at the bottom leg chain, and then deep agents up top So let's go ahead and let's invoke the agent and let's just show that hey okay, let's just show that it can write a file and then I wanted to read about to me. And so we're gonna see that it's going to create a file and then it's going to read it back and so I'm going to see that, okay. 

発話者1  (08:22)
Sweet, so it created this file. I could see it here, and then inside it is this. Hello, from the bathrooms as well. 

発話者1  (08:28)
And so that's just to show you guys where it's actually gonna go ahead and use that rank file tool. Let's add for building a research agent. We need to be able to do some web search right? 

発話者1  (08:40)
So let's add this to Billy's search tool where we can go ahead and allow the agents who go out and search the internet. And for this, let's only have a return Max, of free results. Let's go ahead and add that here and then at the bottom, let's just show a quick test to make sure that that actually works. 

発話者1  (08:58)
And so I'm asking in 2 sentences, what is lanegraph? I'll use one search and so it brings back the response here just to get an actual understanding of if it actually did one search. This is where length said comes in the handy in 2 sentences. 

発話者1  (09:13)
What is length graph? Use one search. Okay, great, so we can see this is the input to that to really search tool. 

発話者1  (09:19)
And then this is the output as well. So I'm happy with that. So we talked about this concept of follow systems, but we haven't really dove deep here, and so now let's spend some time talking about maybe the different file sort of back ends that exist. 

発話者1  (09:34)
And how we would think about using them. And as you build deep agents, so the first concept we have is this concept of a state background. The state back end is default 2 defendants. 

発話者1  (09:45)
It's always there. Reason being is like, let's go back to that tool eviction event that we talked about earlier, if we're gonna do something like that where we evict the tool output to a file system. We need to have this place for that file to go and that's going to be in the state back then. 

発話者1  (10:04)
Who could see it? It's only this threat. So this thread, you could think of a threat as a conversation, right? 

発話者1  (10:10)
So within a conversation I can have multiple of those tool addiction events, or we think back to the offloading the context management piece of dp agents and we can offload the conversation and summarize it, but still keep it, therefore the agent to look up and the reality ISIS that only really pertains to that specific thread. So we just save it by that thread and then when I run it again, I'm not going to be able to see that right. I'm not going to see the output of the tool. 

発話者1  (10:37)
I'm not going to see the conversation that I had earlier. That's going to be suited something like the store back in which I'll talk about in a second. But before we get there, let's talk about a file system back in. 

発話者1  (10:48)
So with deep agents, you could run deep agents code, this would be a coding agent that we use a lot eternally that you can like configure with different models. Maybe with some open source models. And so if we're gonna have a locally running coding agent, we need support to access our file system. 

発話者1  (11:04)
And so, this is great for things like local projects and for running that deep agents, code I mentioned the store back at it. So the store back end is not by thread, but rather it can go across threads, and so this becomes really, really important for like long-term memories. Because in one agent run, I might learn something that I add to a memory's file. 

発話者1  (11:26)
And then the next time I run that agent remember. Let's think back to the emoji case. Now that agent gonna pull-down that Kevin doesn't like emojis and won't send me any emojis and so it's really important for that to be not Perth. 

発話者1  (11:39)
Red, but rather across threads, and so what we can actually do is we can create sort of this best of both world situation with this composite back, end where we still want the state back in right. It's default, it's needed. And that's gonna be where like conversation might go if we can make that or the tool output, if we evict that, but I want to have this like memories that with this store back in it. 

発話者1  (12:02)
So I can have a state back in and a store back in and I can use composite back end to do that and we'll actually go ahead and do that for our D patient here today. So before we get ahead of ourselves, I think it's good to just show this concept that of that state back then. That's default to deep agents. 

発話者1  (12:18)
Let's go ahead and write a file and then in one thread. Let's go ahead and create a brand new thread and show that there is no file that exists. And so here I'm gonna rub this. 

発話者1  (12:27)
But I'm gonna write a file call this back. what this my research findings go up here and so what we're going to see right at first okay, great and thread won that file does exist and thread 2 it's empty, right? So here I ask, hey, can you list all files with the ls tool that you have native? 

発話者1  (12:46)
And we can see that it doesn't exist again, because state back end is just her conversation, her threat, we call it So we talked about file system back into kind of actually using a deep agent to write to our real disk and show. Let's show that working in practice here, and so I'm going to write this notes. Dot txd, with this. 

発話者1  (13:08)
Hello, from Carl system back in, and I want to show that, you know, it's the same contract. The sort of back end protocol that we implement, but we could just have different places that we filed those 2, so you can have it be the state back, then. Store back in that you can have it be this actual file system, or how a lot of people use it in production is maybe at points that store back and could point so like Margo, dp or postcrens, or you have an S3 back end and that roots from S3 So let's go ahead and run this. 

発話者1  (13:37)
We can write this notes out txt to our local file system. We see it exist, and let's go ahead and read it. Okay, great. 

発話者1  (13:42)
It has this hollow from file system back in here as well, and we're gonna go ahead and remove that from my file system. And then so later, we're gonna build that composite back, end that kind of best of both world scenario. So let's go ahead and we talk about some agents a little bit. 

発話者1  (13:59)
But why are sub agents important, especially in the case of a research agent? And so sub agents allows us to do contact isolation, right without a subagent. The maid agent is going to have to do a bunch of work right? 

発話者1  (14:13)
And all of that context is going to get brought into the main agent. And we're using like something like GPU, 54 right? And so that could get expensive, and so what I'd rather do is spin app some subagents that are running in parallel, give them access to tools as well and allow them to go do work, bring in information from the Web and then only give my final report back to the main agent as well. 

発話者1  (14:34)
And I can do that maybe using a cheaper model as the sub agent as well. And so again, this allows for much stronger context, isolation instead of it, having all been done in the month. Main agent, the main agent can decide. 

発話者1  (14:48)
Hey, I'm gonna spin up a couple different sub agents that are gonna go work and then they're going to give me back only the information that I need. Create my research findings. And so the key takeaway here is we can add this summation model attached to 54 minute, let's define it here, so let's add this research agent. 

発話者1  (15:07)
I first take on this demo I only wanted to use 1 and 2 searches maximum, and then I wanted to summarize all that information that I found and give it back to the main agent. Let's go ahead here and add that sub agent, as that research sub agent that we just created and let's go ahead and run this. I want to research what land graph and link chains are, and I want it to give me a one paragraph summary for each and hopefully we're gonna see if it runs. 

発話者1  (15:32)
It gives me a one paragraph summary for each and then we'll pop back into links with and show that it called that task tool that you guys saw earlier one of those subagents that spun off is going to go research lane graph, and the other is going to go research lane chain, and so it's going to do all that work isolated and only bring back the information that it needs and so what we can see here is it came back with this one paragraph summary. Obviously here I can't actually tell what it did so I'm going to pop back here. 

発話者1  (15:59)
2 lengths with we can see okay, research lane, graph and lane chain are and then at the top here we can see the first thing. It did it decided to call the task tool which just spins up the subagent. It's, you know, this research agent, but just has different descriptions. 

発話者1  (16:15)
So, for one it's going to research lane graph and for the other it's going to research language chain, and so again it goes off, it does all of its work isolated. And then it brings back that information to the main Asian as well. We can see if we spin this right, so we have a task, and it's going to do a bunch of things. 

発話者1  (16:31)
It can rent them to news. It's going to call this familiar search tool. It's going to call it a couple times but the reality is, you know, if it does that core context, isolation and then brings back this report here to the main agent, with this inline citation that I asked about earlier so that becomes really, really important, and that's supported, right with deep agents as we have these 4 long run tasks? 

発話者1  (16:50)
We want to make sure that we support some agents for context isolation. He talked about human and loop, and I said, hey, we need human and loop. We'll take questions at the end of the year so we have human in the loop, right? 

発話者1  (17:02)
And so for when we have support to work with our file system, when I'm a little scared because it ever writes a file or edits a file I want to make sure I have to approve it and so basically we can do this using the concept of interrupts and basically we can decide, okay. Let's create a deep agent. Let's say that anytime the agent decides to call the right file tool or the edit file tool. 

発話者1  (17:28)
Then, it has to cause the execution of their agent and has to wait. And it has the weight for me to approve it. And so some real life applications of this is like we saw langsmith tweet earlier at the keynote as well. 

発話者1  (17:41)
And so a lot of folks at length use linksmith tweet to maybe do some things, and then the final output of it is, I want you to respond to an email but the reality is we don't want that send_. Email tool, uh to allow the agents who just write whatever you want and then set it off, I want the agent to write the email, but when it calls that sudden email tool, I want it to pause and wait for me to come back into place and hit approve and so let's go ahead and show this here where I'm going to write a file call. 

発話者1  (18:12)
This\ est out at the throwback to the hello world days and what we're gonna see is this agent basically has to wait, it's not going to do anything that interrupts gets triggered, and so at the bottom here, the agent decided that it wants to call this right file tool. Here are the arguments to that tool. And then here are the different options that I have. 

発話者1  (18:32)
I can either approve it. I can edit it, or I can reject it so right now, the art agent is just waiting. It's paused until I come back, and I actually say to approve that file being written. 

発話者1  (18:45)
And so if we go here, I'm going to mimic basically hitting a UI button right that says approve, and we're gonna go ahead and hit approve, and let's go ahead. And the fact that it actually exists in that state background that you guys saw earlier? So great. 

発話者1  (18:59)
The file is now at state and then let's read from it. Okay, it's hello, world so great. So that's basically to show you guys, you know, you need to be using that human in the loop middleware horse certain tools, because maybe we have this like right? 

発話者1  (19:10)
2 database tool and so, you know, you want to use deep agents, but you don't feel comfortable. That you're trusted to sort of write the information to the database, and so we can use something like the human middleware to define what tools you need to have interrupts, what tools need to have human and the loop approval. Okay, so let's go back to long-term memory. 

発話者1  (19:34)
So we've talked a lot about like memory is really, really important. I brought up that concept of like card code. For example, I don't want any emojis coming back, and it saves us to this memory file, you know, kind of where we're going with agents. 

発話者1  (19:47)
Right? Is this concept of like agents improving themselves over time? And so if agents are going to improve themselves over time, they need a place to send their improvements to and then to pick back up in a different conversation or invocation of that agent, for example. 

発話者1  (20:04)
And so we have this concept of maybe we want to add this\\memory style that an agent can write memories to and read from in different invocation of the agent, and that uses this concept of a store Becket, again, it's persistent across threads, but we still need that safe. Becket, that only lasts within that single thread for those things like tool eviction events, for maybe the conversation getting off, that conversation gets offloaded, I don't want it to go to squirbeck and I don't want it across threads, I only care about that within a thread, but something like memories, where that's really gonna be, how an Asian improves itself. 

発話者1  (20:42)
Over time, I do want to pick it up in future versions of that agent, and so if we tied it back also to the human in the loop that we saw earlier, maybe I'm not comfortable with the agent, always writing to the memories file by itself. And so you can add sort of like, you know, the human elope that says, hey, when you write file when you write that memory file, I want to approve it. And so that way you kind of get that human and loop to see like what does the agent want to do to sort of or what is it learning about me Uber time, for example? 

発話者1  (21:12)
And so let's go ahead here, let's create this concept of the composite background that I talked about. Earlier where the default is going to be the state back end again, we need it right. We need it for the school eviction events, but I want to route anything that this\\memories to this concept of a store back at and so let's go ahead, I've run an invocation of this agent. 

発話者1  (21:32)
I want to save some important notes to this memory's folder. And then we'll show that the file outside of those sort of disappear. When the conversation ends and so in thread, one here, I'm gonna save this AI. 

発話者1  (21:46)
Agents are evolving rapidly in 2026. Through this memory folder and then we're going to see that, okay, this thread so we had it saved to that folder. We can see in the store back end. 

発話者1  (21:58)
We do have this folder file and folder it does exist. But there's nothing that was saved to the state that back in so it doesn't exist. And then let's go ahead. 

発話者1  (22:08)
Let's invoke our agent and let's go ahead and use that store back and honor second thread and let's read from the memories that we've created. And so here I want to say, hey, in a different implication, right? So I'm creating a brand new threat. 

発話者1  (22:21)
But I want to show that the memory persists can you read me? What's in this\\memories folder here and so let's go ahead and do it, and let's show that we're actually reefs from that itself. So we can see in thread. 

発話者1  (22:35)
2, we have okay, sweet AI agents are evolving rapidly in 2026. And so again, this is going to be how you guys are starting to get some unlocks and agents to allow them to remember things Uber time. The last little bit that we'll talk about today. 

発話者1  (22:49)
Is this concept of like agents.md and skills and how do these relate to system problems? Right? Because I think you know, not too long ago, we were all thinking about creating prompts and now in prompt engineering. 

発話者1  (22:59)
And now we're thinking about how context works, right in context engineering. And we're kind of hereson talked about the stay where you kind of pick whatever model you want, you pick the hardest. And then you kind of need the context as well, and those three things are really just what make up an agent. 

発話者1  (23:14)
So let's talk about sister crops, right? Sister crops are always loaded into the context window of our agent. And so I showed you guys that earlier, right when we peeked underneath the hood of create deep agent, we see that we have a system prompt, and I'll go ahead. 

発話者1  (23:27)
And show you guys what the system prompt, that deep agents look like. It is not editable by the agent, right? So if you use system_prompt, it's never going to be edible and so this is great for something like the system, prompt of deep ages right? 

発話者1  (23:40)
I don't want it to ever be changed. He just thought idea is something that's become kind of popular, standardized across the East Asian harnesses, and so this is loaded, always in the context window. So I'll show you guys, but you have your system prompt. 

発話者1  (23:56)
And then when you add this agent 7D file, we're going to pend that to the prompt itself. And this is editable by the agent, and so this ends up being a place that the agent can learn over time. Maybe rewrite some its instructions based on what we're learning. 

発話者1  (24:12)
I come from a larger enterprise before this that probably sounds scary to a lot of you guys, and so that's where we think about those file system permissions, right? So maybe when we change the agents out on D you all need to approve it instead of just allowing it to change Uber time and then we have skills, right? Like, we're kind of conferging on skills being really, really important and so skills are sort of loaded on demand right? 

発話者1  (24:35)
So that uses that read file tool that's data to deep agents, and it only brings in the skill when it decides that it need. So let's go ahead and show an example of it sort of needing to read in that skill here. So let's create an agent's thought and B you know, we can think of this as like, again, that editable prompt as well, I think, honestly, there's like some interesting things in the future that will figure out of like whoa, what's kind of the difference between like our system? 

発話者1  (25:03)
Props and our agents thought I'd be, and I still think we're honestly kind of figuring out that ourselves and then we have the skill. So let's add a LinkedIn skill that basically takes the research that we've done, but formats it into sort of a linkediny style. Maybe add some hashtags at the end and so let's go ahead and add that in what we also could do here again and I talked about this earlier is maybe we have a LinkedIn skill. 

発話者1  (25:28)
But we also have a link chain block skill, maybe we have a Twitter post skill. So the research is the same, but the place that we sort of send that research to is different. And so if I had you know, I probably should have added multiple skills to this to show you guy is that what I want to write a LinkedIn scope, it only reads in that context again, just shaving a little bit on context window saving on cost. 

発話者1  (25:50)
So let's go ahead and run this here. We're gonna add that agents that I need. Let's add those skill file and then let's go ahead and run. 

発話者1  (25:58)
Let's briefly research what light chain is, and then let's write a short LinkedIn post about them. And let's see if our skill actually was loaded in and let's see what that agent's thought MD looks like in the system as well. And so this is gonna take a little bit to run, but the idea here again, is it's gonna go off. 

発話者1  (26:14)
It's gonna go do some work, and you know, the work is going to be done. And we're gonna realize okay, cool, like we also want to write a short LinkedIn post about them. And hopefully we're gonna see that I have a LinkedIn post here, I've got the lovely emojis that I don't like, but I never prompted, it should not have that. 

発話者1  (26:30)
And so here we can see that this is gonna be my LinkedIn post as well, and so if we go back to link Smith and we go back to the latest invocation, we could see I briefly researched what lane chain is then write a short link to post about them. So right away, it decided that it wanted to read file that file is that LinkedIn post skill that I just mentioned earlier. So now it actually brings the context of that into the context window that has some ideas of what it wants, how long it should be. 

発話者1  (26:58)
And then if we go back, I mentioned, let's take a look at the system prompt of the actual deep agent itself. And we can see here, this is the actual underlying system prompt of the Asian, and then I want to go ahead and make sure that my agent's out indeed is actually in that context window on all times and I'm gonna keep scrolling. And we're gonna see that the agents out ID that I talked about earlier is loaded in. 

発話者1  (27:22)
It's this research assistant's right. And I'm gonna give it these instructions here as well, and so that's a way that you can use. You're obviously going to always have that base system prompted the deep agents how to use the tools. 

発話者1  (27:32)
But then you can add in specific information around the use case that you guys are creating as well. So let's jump back to the notebook. I know we have about 4 or 5 minutes here. 

発話者1  (27:44)
I'll make sure I'll wrap the set. So we have time for questions. And so the other things that we can do, if we're kind of working through the snowbook, maybe what I work through next is we can use this lanegraft Dev command and we could then run this in langsmith to show what are the middleware actually being run and sort of when the skills are being read in and so this makes sure that you don't bounce back between, you know, your sort of interminal or in visual studio code and then you go somewhere else to take a look at what's happened and you could do this all within the links that studios, well I mentioned. 

発話者1  (28:14)
Maybe on write more skills, because I'd have like a lane chain block skill I've had maybe the Twitter blog skill, one block skill again that we use all the time at lane shade. Is this lane chain brand skill. So you know, we're kind of converging that hdml is really, really nice for presentations, so go out do that research, and then at the end, read this link chain brand scale that tells you what colors we use what fonts we use and then convert that research into like an hgml and that's how we honestly all generate presentations today, and then maybe you want to have per user memory, right? 

発話者1  (28:45)
So what we saw earlier? There's just this like\\memories, but you want to have like namespaces so that some of those memories are just by user, or maybe you also want some that are by like an organization or by an agent, and so you probably would create a more robust system for memories as well. And then maybe we'll do something we add more different subagents, but I'll ask for now that one sub agent is good for me. 

発話者1  (29:10)
So again, if I were to wrap this up, we talked about earlier how AI is honestly is offloading a lot of our thinking, but it can't offload our understanding again. So hopefully coming out of this, you guys have a better understanding of what the actual components are going on under the hood in deep agents. So that when you say you're telling your coding agent, hey, build a deep agent using this, you actually have an understanding of what's going on underneath the hood. 

発話者1  (29:34)
So thank you guys. Thanks for being with me. Thanks for being here. 

発話者1  (29:37)
I know the conference. That's about to wrap up, but I really, really appreciate you guys being here today. So thank you, and then we'll ask some questions as well. 

発話者1  (29:44)
I think there's a wife that's going to get passed 

発話者2  (29:52)
around. Thank you really interesting. Do you have a good mental model for when you should use? 

発話者2  (29:58)
Like multiple skill directories Vs multiple subagenes? For instance, you had like a research subagent, but you could also do that with like a research skill. So there's some sort of decision boundary between skills and 8 

発話者1  (30:13)
subagenes. But yeah, I think the like key distinction so you could have muscle. Like you could have a research skill that tells it how to do research, but that research skill is going to be brought into like the main agent, for example, and then it's going to go out, search a bunch of the Web in parallel and then bring all of that context back in and then it's gonna synthesize its results. 

発話者1  (30:34)
If you have sub agents, you can then kick off a subagent to go research lanking. Okay, go off to work. Go research lane, graph go off and do work, and then there. 

発話者1  (30:42)
It's going to have the context all come into its window and only send back the summary. So I like my idea is like for research. Some agents are great but honestly in a lot of cases, it's good to just like give skills to the main agent as well. 

発話者1  (30:56)
So that, yeah, because it's a tricky balance between like context isolation, but then also that handoff is something that's really tricky between like a main agent and a sub 

発話者2  (31:05)
agent. A quick quick follow-up for that. Can a skill trigger a subagen 

発話者1  (31:11)
delegation? Oh, that's a good question. I think yeah so what you could do is like, in a skill, you could tell it that, you know, it reads it and then maybe in certain cases all you could basically have in the skill is you can tell it to call subagen. 

発話者1  (31:24)
Because underneath the hood, when it's gonna do it, just call that task tool that we saw earlier so maybe in certain cases, we say okay, if I name it bad example. But if I want to write a LinkedIn post, bring in that in and that in that there's just text right. And then there's just text. 

発話者1  (31:38)
And that text might say, kick off a subagent that writes in the LinkedIn format again, bad example. But could theoretically do it because you're just bringing instructions into the context window. So yeah, absolutely 

発話者2  (31:50)
absolutely. Thank you. Skill modules for the 

発話者1  (32:04)
coat. So I think we have time for a couple more questions here. Thank you a great 1 can subage and be an ang graph. 

発話者1  (32:13)
Yeah, definitely. So I think that's, you know, a really interesting pattern. Where it could be this again, models and a little bit tools, but maybe it's like the more deterministic workflow that you guys may used to creating with players. 

発話者1  (32:25)
All right, maybe one more 

発話者3  (32:27)
question. Yeah, so there's so the state packet and the store packet. I believe the fenced explicitly for it to read the memories file. 

発話者3  (32:36)
The findings file to read something. Yeah, so does the stool pack and get read automatically. There's a agent decide that I need to use this, or do we need to explicitly invoke 

発話者1  (32:46)
it? And that's a good question. I believe that is going to basically be like the file and that the agent has to decide. 

発話者1  (32:54)
Okay, I want to bring in that to the context 

発話者3  (32:58)
window. A section of 3 create me watch and memory find exerdity. If I had said, what are your findings from your memory? 

発話者3  (33:03)
What has probably 

発話者1  (33:05)
done I think right? Yeah, but you know, when you define that agent side and D for example, when you define the memory equals agent side of D that always is in the context window of the agent. Yeah, cool, well, thank you guys so much. 

発話者1  (33:18)
Thanks for being here. I'll stick around because I know I probably couldn't answer all your questions. We also have Colin and Mason right here. 

発話者1  (33:24)
As well who'll get answer any questions that you guys have also. So thank you 

発話者0  (33:28)
guys. 
