
発話者1  (00:00)
Hello, everyone happy Wednesday. It's the middle of the week. And then I believe that data science correction for safety and customer care at led and my team is including AI assist, which is our customer care. 

発話者1  (00:21)
AI agents are years and I'm here to talk to you about how we build a system that actually helps to scale AI agent in production. So maybe just a quick show of time, how many of you here should a lot of I'm literally guilty of that. So like, don't be embarrassed, I know, it's one of those things that We always forgot about really should hopefully. 

発話者1  (00:51)
You know, doesn't need any additional introductions. Hopefully everyone in the circle, but just a couple statistics about, you know, we have 79070 9 million trips a month. And our AI exists. 

発話者1  (01:06)
Today, there's about 270000 AI intervention per month. We became able to build AI agents and board Russians of the production rate. 65%. 

発話者1  (01:19)
And AI resolution rates that 35%, 35% like sleep a little bit low, but we really thought ourselves were really high. R we want the Asians to solve the customer fully and to M and not just like blog customers on each support. Should you all have experience with that with support chat? 

発話者1  (01:41)
So I'm gonna quickly walk you through ais. As this journey, you know, we started this journey in 20. We used very simple deterministic logic back then. 

発話者1  (01:54)
So imagine if you say a the body is going to say B back to you, but we all now have album has really transformed transformed the state and with either being able to build more than 7 AI agents in the past. And Our resolution rate has really gone out from 10% to 35% income. I'll just give you a sense of what type of AI should be building at length no provider. 

発話者1  (02:21)
We have agents that handle charges to fill complaints and experience. If you ever have a driver that has smoke even car, you can report to us on the driver's side. You know, you have automated - claim processing compliance setups down the yellow you have taxes. 

発話者1  (02:39)
We also love doing that. I just want to show a couple like really agents that I thought was really interesting. That with those and also shut up to actually this is not the problem down here, who, actually on my team who built this AI agent. 

発話者1  (02:58)
Because this agent on the driver's side, that is a multimodal complex AI agent that when the driver outlook photos of the damaged plan. On the righter side, we have agent that literally processes 80 class automation or refast logic in the back end and able to contextually, based on what the right way is telling us and what their situations are explain our refund decision to them. In very similar ways All that is to say is, you know, we wouldn't have had to be able to shift so many AI agents or And make sure that such complex AI agents actually perform in productions right without a great genome system. 

発話者1  (03:45)
Closer here, a little s***, patriotism. So I'm not going to walk you through. As this architecture, you know, it's land check land route landscape. 

発話者1  (04:00)
Some pinot and you know that, but I'm more interested to talk to you about How we think about it, or how you shift our brain production system, right? A little bit found myself I've been You know, for my career, I can do data science for the while I've been building machine learning model and my approach to thinking about AI is up for AI. Agent is no different than traditional analytics. 

発話者1  (04:34)
So for those of you who come from deep science background and now engineering background, we're used to working in the notebook, you throw out this model. You train on a huge data set. You have some kind of ground truth or regression path, and then you run this offline evaluation, right? 

発話者1  (04:51)
And see what the performance are should be shifted. We now shift. Think about this as part of the week right? 

発話者1  (04:57)
Can we launch? So I really want to emphasize on the top line upline ethos, if that estimate is the way that we do nl engineering for the last couple of years, why should AI engineers be any different? Really feeling about that. 

発話者1  (05:13)
And The offline you know, really served as a quality policy gauge. You don't want to use your loser as test data, but maybe if you're a startup, you have podcast information, that's okay so I have been able to skip at the scale of flip. We really don't want to use our customer as well. 

発話者1  (05:35)
And once you know, we got the agent in production. We have continuous monitoring. We have our online data getting our demand sen. 

発話者1  (05:43)
Tracers, human in the world, all that good stuff that's giving us feedback of the groups. So I'm gonna go into each of these components looking a little bit more details Thinking about offline valuations are, what does that mean? How is it different for traditional ML engineering world? 

発話者1  (06:05)
You know, we love working in the book. We launch this shopping model. ESP 5 and then get a graphic right. 

発話者1  (06:14)
So for AI engineering, this is a little bit more set up there. We really took inspiration from how bench, which fantastic team at Sierra AI, has published as a public benchmark that over the album model for the other aircraft are using us as benchmark. So for Chris offline evaluations, I'd like to build a lightweight simulator so I'll be right here we have our bedrock Asia, which is, you know, the AI agent that we've built for AI exists. 

発話者1  (06:48)
And then we have album user, for we just use model album models to grow play users so that we can generate this entertainment trajectory of an interaction. And then we have The way we use a very copy driven approach, we have a Yale found that specify, you know what the user intensified. What is the support scenarios that we are looking at? 

発話者1  (07:17)
How do we mock the state of the world? Because they talk like you're not calling. You're making networks called to sort of mcp, so in offline setting, where marking those mcp data outputs, and imagining it that agent or offline creates such smart mccr, with one of the things that's on the funky car. 

発話者1  (07:41)
So we've got this long channel trajectory of all the muted salon copies. It is a computation, so like different accommodations, different deep cry, the state of the world, the user intends a Priscilla, and then the goal here really is to get a diversity of effects that you can use through phosphate production data out you want to offline via good process of how the agent is going to perform, when you actually turn it off. So when a trajectory will certify an evaluator L we use L as a judge I think everyone is doing that cook assertion. 

発話者1  (08:22)
You know, we found something simple, simple tracking script that checks the And state of the world season conditions met upon classic failure. I'll get into Alvin Josh. Hello, you know, I think when we started thinking about Ellen judge, and I'm sure that everyone here is looking to my Lens or any other stability platform you see Different platforms framework comes with like a 3 billion set of L and judge. 

発話者1  (08:55)
Ray things like toxicity, store response, calculus, compensation, conciseness, and things like that, we kind of you know, we kind of started the same way as well. We were defining things like 2 years appropriate nerves, response pathways, naturalness and all that type. And these are based score on the scale of 0 to 1. 

発話者1  (09:18)
So like a scalar scale metrics, so what's the what's the problem with this right? For response helpfulness, for example, was does a 0.4 score compared to 2.7, right? How can you? 

発話者1  (09:36)
How can you move the veto, right? And if you want to move your overall score, what the product inside is this giving you So with being very humanity in the battle, what Alec, the judge should do Alphabet quickly, you know the ones easy into the city for options in Asian infractions. So the way that we think about how we judge is that it should be framed around the past that you want the AI to perform, right, so your AI vision is being structured through cost AB. 

発話者1  (10:15)
And C and each of those tasks that also doesn't fail like return So very simple example I'm going to go from Our landscape platform is this educational educational rate set acquired the task that we want our AI to do is to educate the user about lip policy. You know, right charters, large, some other Tempest course scenario crisis. So the benefit of doing this is defining, very clear success criteria for your agent, and by default defining a rubric, like this. 

発話者1  (10:49)
When you see interruption that fell the rubric, you can very clearly quickly know that while someone feels right. And that becomes actionable inside what becomes far inside the house you're checking your engineering team to improve your AI agent fickle, problems, fickle tool, change your control or logic or Walmart, and you rather look against you through So this is just not a novel break that I want to play quickly show Okay, another thing that we really struggle with is, you know, how do we trust these elements and judge right when we define, we define some profit. 

発話者1  (11:32)
But how do we know it's to be the right thing. So my own personal things that, well, we just treat our and judge like a machine learning model. Right? 

発話者1  (11:42)
You collect some you collect some human label, ground sugar from the bag expert about, you know how score how scores are in production based on appropriate? And you go through this traditional ML engineering, look, change the problem. Change your reasoning, theater lines in the human and human ingredients for and the way it does that you have Alan judge. 

発話者1  (12:07)
That's a language human So, you know, a little offline simulator what else can go wrong, right? So, very early about we use artificial shell. You know, cloth model and AI model to grow play as a user, but oftentimes what we see is as you can see here, you know, the Ellen, not being nice, helpful assistant. 

発話者1  (12:34)
They explain their issues very nicely to our AI agents that are guilty of this as far as I don't typically do this. When I reach out to support Most often than not when we were the preventive prevention. We see productions are at 1 or 2 words, right? 

発話者1  (12:51)
People are very impatient, people don't sit down and thank you explain their issues. So when we did this, our first AI issue was giving us 90% pass rates to launch, right. In the enforcement actually launching projects. 

発話者1  (13:09)
So what can we do to fix this right? This is a pretty active research area. Small Microsoft, publishing paper. 

発話者1  (13:20)
How you should be training your album album user using real world information. So this is essentially what we are planning to do and live this fall. With actively looking into our model, that's aligning living sort of savings for their speaker, more like a user, technically making out, in doubt, a little bit more difficult, your benchmarks or might go down. 

発話者1  (13:45)
But you really want this to be a good toxic production. Otherwise, the point Another thing that we are looking to work for Congress, actually not is defining clear percent networks. And this will be used to ground All right, quickly talk I want to talk about how that Smith really helps. 

発話者1  (14:11)
First, manage how we now work tracing Elon Musk, automation application tools. If you're hearing about advanced, I'll just quickly speak through this because I'm running outside. You know, Tracy, I think smile has been brought up multiple times previous concentrations. 

発話者1  (14:32)
But we, you know, offspring, assimilation and our online online bronze in productions. We're using transmission to have a capture these nice trajectory, this, because really nice training data for a model later off as well as a good interface for operation key groups, mentally advocating that behavior. The elevator this is problematic. 

発話者1  (14:58)
Ellen judge that we use for our Hong Kong simulator as well as for luxury art. Animatrician queue, that's one modern, nice bellland students that we have automation enlarged it. So for traces that they'll, you know, judge criteria. 

発話者1  (15:15)
We can set our automation and that apps in fell traces to an adaptation cube, and here we have our operations being set app on this annotation queue to help us memory label. This example of ngos, we'll go in and analyze what are the genetic variable. And that's feeds back into how we can improve copyright. 

発話者1  (15:40)
All right. So what's next for AI? Is this correct? 

発話者1  (15:44)
We've done a lot of ancient engineers that means I've managing the contact, but managing the farms. Right? That's the Chinese force. 

発話者1  (15:51)
Nowadays managing the farmers around a model which is basically everything around model. Weather Rap type I and 2 definitions, graph and frog and Olaf. Oh, and we've been running our points to later as more of like a lightweight script upline. 

発話者1  (16:10)
Hell. Now there's a concept of inaugural harness that we can define that can help us manage our evaluation from offline more effectively. Hell does so far for all the traces that we've been collecting so far, we've been using it to feed into car inside that help us improve our agent, improve our harness, but we haven't really done much on water training, updating the way that the album model and train a customer album or is. 

発話者1  (16:42)
That that model at this area Hiking is powerful, so that's how we close the book from the email pack. All right, thank you. Everyone has more combat about being out there at the tool if you want to speak to me and love talking about talk to me and pray and see 

発話者2  (17:23)
Thank you, Nick, we'll now have an 80 minute lunch break. Join us back here at 1:40 PM today, from China, visiting available album Michigan Street and we have language leaders in these video team in the long-term interview for Oscar 
