
発話者1  (00:01)
Who is going to discuss the sec's dignity? 

発話者2  (00:29)
All right, hello, my name is Danna and I'm an engineer in fc daily talking about I see, is a subsided marketplace where millions of merchants sell and crafted for vintage items. 86 billion lives 13, through our inventory has special talents. Because our inventory is It's actually operating the item instead of structured descriptions that are sometimes fluttered at winds. 

発話者2  (01:16)
Also, many of the important details are passionate and visuals, such as personal images and search benefits a lot from expertise as our inventory has From high marks tandem, so having an expert in able to rob it originally, search queries is very useful. For these reasons, we believe that nature will be very advantageous for conversational search particular, wanting to focus on gifted as we know. If things are puzzling process where we may know each specific, want to give a gift to, but we may not have a particular idea of what to give. 

発話者2  (02:08)
So the idea is that our agents with air with shoppers and collaboratively and iteratively, provides recommendations on the gift. So we've developed this agent and released its data and perception and what we found was that it returns high quality search results of relatively good harness. It also results in a relatively high purchase rates in our own business. 

発話者2  (02:48)
So today, I'm going to go to the NASA bolts and how we built this patient focusing on engineering evalu. And the plant. With respect to engineering challenges, we have problems that the areas of reliability Henry madden heard speed. 

発話者2  (03:08)
A first study is why 2 exclusion architecture Let me show the climate change. Because as a class first a class of anchor space, it also provides for agent data of circulability and evaluation. I also provided an optionality, which is an important accord for us today. 

発話者2  (03:31)
As we deal with rising, broken costs as well as tissues that model capacity Charles of engineering design, we wanted to start a simple as possible. Looking at classically justified, we started 1KP1 react, which was a nice combination of different amounts of abstraction. So lots of memories of our zip kids He was the most gradual balance. 

発話者2  (04:06)
That's 2 men on the athletes. Given a request model I pitched schools from a Pope after a vocation that was decent about the results that he was continued with the full cost of return and curated this event. The perspective of the tools, multiple tools for review. 

発話者2  (04:37)
Canada's 13th and union listings are memory. For example, finding saving information about saving profiles The skills so the model, the dynamic field of instructions of how to use the skills for people. So let's go to engineering challenge solutions that we have along the way, authentic So one of the early talks we had was repeated, who called by the model. 

発話者2  (05:16)
The same specific tool, our solution was to straighten the middle that has some matching condition, displaced repeated tool costs, and then intervenes at different levels of degrees depending on the severity of this particular example of the model. Seed where the model has repeated tools. So And then after I repeated the calls I'm a little aware So it's the same problem, scrub the model to synthesize or ask them to use a former language. 

発話者2  (05:58)
And after 10 repeatable calls the middle ground basin air has to be used there to buy them. Another example of a model about the labor earlier was History that hallucinations, whether it will be certain cases for the model. For example, the term truncated risk of evidence and our solution. 

発話者2  (06:23)
Here is to have our tools. For example, search listings record, a set of observed 90s in a lecture, and then after the model runs the middle word piece that input curated a set of ids to model out comparatively with the observed ids that collection. Then, the middleware basis, those ibs capture the earthquake And that was an example of electric class dealing with reliable model outputs. 

発話者2  (06:57)
Here's an example of unreliable model memory management. So we found that the model has dropped our significant feature For example, the store featured size of nerves and secrets. So to divide and resolve this, you created a terminal. 

発話者2  (07:19)
Why agent conductor and this provides the ability to the agent's agent store are actively also being integrated with hypotheses made up together, so it allows for semantic breakfast point to, for example, rate points. In addition, we also see the protest act This allowed us to buy seven or eight different issues. Create solutions as creating modern literature, conscriptive species that we see So I talked about moving back and liabilities. 

発話者2  (08:02)
Now let's talk about these price. So ideally, we would like to stream the results from the land graph pages back to THE client. However, our egg grass cell appointed exists in a relatively new Hoover network. 

発話者2  (08:22)
We didn't want to have to be equipped oftentimes just for that cluster. In addition to the viable security protections in order to expose it to the internet. On the other hand we have our pre-existing mobstanding SD Webster. 

発話者2  (08:42)
However, this sort of is useful for service regulatory plus however, it was attached and a patch was a sign. They were running along the press. So our architecture routine came up with the steam socket pass path that allows us to use artistic The way it looks is that given a climate request ph, D the action worker over tests to take a request has moral requests that pass the biologists through a long run demon. 

発話者2  (09:21)
I was running in a cyclone. At that point after that handoff did actually broke her It's pretty at least that the long run is DNA is responsible for screening updates? That's faster than possible. 

発話者2  (09:35)
This way, we can reduce artistic websites, infrastructure search like that extreme So I talked about how bills are in patients having to spread out the evaluated 2 parts of evaluation running through the trajectory. Factory, in addition to standard integration of units has created a test using both a model romantic test. A hide and ensure that the past rate the vehicle passed rates is above some pressure. 

発話者2  (10:17)
So, for example, given a salary test that tests that the agent calls get shot pooled. The prospective outcomes, we want to assure that the listings or the relevant profile shopper. In terms of budget space, particularly, we wanted to create an LLM judge, aligned for a whole data set. 

発話者2  (10:50)
But there's a lot of challenges with respect to methodology. For example, how do we generate diverse data set, how do we align for There's a calorie, so it enables a system way to be the way data engagement. Train elements such as automatic data set and what prescription efforts can be used for application Ideally, we would have intimidated schooling that operational license models that could be used by all the engineers activity, melodies and product engineers. 

発話者2  (11:30)
So we created an escape, just sell a lot at leverages. Okay A streamlining is the entire evaluation of this can be used by both engineers. Also, agents. 

発話者2  (11:46)
So then you talk to you about each stage of this work. Quote the tools that we develop along the way. So we've created a batch and seeing this patch sterilized, but I'm multiple uses of notation generators. 

発話者2  (12:01)
Datasets can be used not only for is that generation but also as generations. For example, running an agent of lost our entire inventory or promote testing for productionizing the way it works is that you have a paralle. And distributed. 

発話者2  (12:21)
A standalone quest to be able to have a service that makes them appointment And that same surface in these real times and actual quests. So this way, there's no risk of offline Vs online fifth, yet consistent, including governance and observability. And we avoided the conducted protocol in the private principle because we could use the same claim. 

発話者2  (12:51)
For angry space and ambiguation. So once we generated that data set When we had emergence of label. This involvement of each example. 

発話者2  (13:05)
2 years is really important to calibrate your reviewers so that they enable system when subjection is to use statistics like as apa measure alignment alpha alignment. A chance, especially important which distribution of samples osteoplastics is very skewed. That would be created training validation and test splits in plant scripts using epistemic best practices like LLM optimization such as funny report. 

発話者2  (13:44)
Guys full for a lineup that John is 2 basketballs. Is that using automated optimization techniques such as Gen. Jews and llms or flat on the judge's errors and spectrum? 

発話者2  (14:01)
This allows the standard effort related to decision and recognition Throughout this process and spent by essential for understanding the judgments of the album and also for understanding the judgment's ability Filey wants to be attacked ourselves, judge the music with our classification school outside and other production. So once we are valuation tomorrow Asians, you can complain with compass and production. All right, the climate system works in the context of the agents models. 

発話者2  (14:45)
This enables automatic Egypt discovery, and it creates a cicv pipeline. Dynamic hotel forms required all one has to specify the damp file for specifyable resources for the appointment of those system uses for the climate data guides to apply skills and reliable bets. Because it took us six weeks apart to pay on launch a reduction. 

発話者2  (15:19)
This was really established by 19 extractions. And this platform that it became about these senior engineers at 1 designer Summary, nature framework and Angels the development of reliable ages, the observability and standard interfaces for customization, for example, as application level. An insurance reliability through deterministic checks may glucose in middle area, as opposed to that. 

発話者2  (15:52)
Ask llms through soon. Some of the path functionality, not the modularity of that middleware makes it easy to swamp in and out. It's a lot more level. 

発話者2  (16:04)
They still provide foundational services and tools. Naturally, we want to build integrations and also customization that those tools are internal workflows that are internal systems doing so was the Finally, as a platform engineer integrated, a products team who develop in East Asia, it was a very effective way of defining requirements for particularly platform development. A landfill technology was released as the court maintains T also give a shout out to albals and work highlights on these particular damage. 

発話者2  (16:54)
So thank you, and I'm happy to ask you questions at the booth during the break. Please. 
